Roots run deep.
Akar menghujam dalam.
- Will! - Come on, Mom.
- Will! - Ayolah, Bu.
- We're almost there. - Will!
- Hampir sampai. - Will!
- You're so fast. - Mom, there it is.
- Kau kencang sekali. - Bu, itu dia!
I can't keep up. You need to be in the Olympics.
Aku tertinggal. Kau layak ikut Olimpiade.
Let's go, Mom. We're so close.
Ayo, Bu. Jaraknya dekat.
Thank you for taking me to see Jett's new billboard.
Terima kasih mengantarku melihat baliho baru Jett.
- Jett's huge! - Will, say "cheese."
- Jett hebat! - Will, bilang "buncis".
- Will for three. - Ah, ah, ah.
- Will cetak 3 angka. - Ah, ah, ah.
Okay, boy, don't be doing all of that now.
Oke, Nak, jangan lakukan itu sekarang.
All right. Guess it's time to go.
Baiklah. Saatnya pergi.
You have to go to work, right?
Kau harus bekerja, 'kan?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. One second.
Woi, sebentar.
Wait, turn it around.
Tunggu, balikkan badannya.
I got it! There we go. Okay.
Dapat! Begitu. Oke.
How about you and I
Bagaimana jika kita
watch the Thorns from inside the stadium?
menonton Thorns dari dalam stadion?
'Cause I'm taking my baby
Karena kubawa sayangku
to see his very first, yep, roarball game!
nonton laga perdana, ya, bola raung!
What?
Apa?
Is this for real?
Ini nyata?
I mean... ...unless you're busy?
Maksudku... ...kecuali kau sibuk?
Oh, baby.
Oh, Sayang.
Aw, it's okay. Thank you.
Aw, tidak apa-apa. Terima kasih.
Thank you so much. I love you, Mom.
Terima kasih banyak. Aku menyayangimu, Bu.
I love you too, Will.
Aku juga menyayangimu, Will.
Let's go, Mom. Come on.
Ayo, Bu. Cepat.
- Roots run deep. - Yeah, let's go!
- Akar menghujam dalam. - Ya, ayo!
Oh. It's right here. Right here. Come on.
Oh. Di sini. Di sini. Ayo.
Mom, stop it.
Bu, hentikan.
Whoo! Let's go!
Whoo! Ayo!
Welcome to the Greenhouse!
Selamat datang di Rumah Kaca!
It's starting!
Mulai!
Are you ready?
Kalian siap?
- Who is the GOAT?
- Siapa sang legenda?
Who is truly the GOAT?
Siapa legenda sejati?
♪ Yeah, thinkin' that it Happened overnight, it didn't ♪
♪ Ya, mengira ini terjadi Instan, padahal tidak ♪
♪ In it for the long-haul Flight, committed ♪
♪ Berjuang jangka panjang Siap berkomitmen ♪
♪ Look, wait ♪
♪ Lihat, tunggu ♪
Introducing Vineland's very own,
Memperkenalkan kebanggaan Vineland,
the hometown hero, a five-time all-star,
pahlawan lokal, 5 kali bintang utama,
Jett Fillmore.
Jett Fillmore.
Yeah! Let's go, Vineland.
Ya! Ayo, Vineland.
Let's go, Jett!
Ayo, Jett!
Having a good time, Will? Baby?
Senang, Will? Sayang?
That's gonna be me, Mom.
Itu aku nanti, Bu.
When I get big, I'm gonna be just like her.
Saat besar nanti, aku akan sepertinya.
One... Yeah!
Satu... Ya!
It's the power of the mind. Your body's not tired.
Ini kekuatan pikiran. Tubuhmu tak lelah.
You can take a break. Don't take a break.
Boleh istirahat. Jangan istirahat.
You got this.
Kau pasti bisa.
Keep pushing.
Terus tekan.
I'm okay!
Aku baik saja!
Hey, Will. Are you working out?
Hei, Will. Sedang latihan?
Hey, Theo. You know it.
Hei, Theo. Tentu saja.
Jett Fillmore doesn't take a day off, and neither do I.
Jett tak pernah libur, begitu juga aku.
My dad said you can't play roarball
Ayahku bilang kau tak bisa main
'cause you're too small.
karena terlalu mungil.
Everyone says that, Theo.
Semua orang bilang begitu.
When I'm on the Thorns,
Saat aku di Thorns,
you'll be courtside, my bro-dent.
kau duduk di pinggir, Sob.
Heck, yeah.
Tentu saja.
Go, Thorns!
Majulah, Thorns!
Hey! Will!
Hei! Will!
I hope you're not trying to sneak out...
Kuharap kau tak mencoba kabur...
...without paying your rent.
...tanpa bayar sewa.
Ooh. Yeah. Um...
Ooh. Ya. Um...
I'll get it to you as soon as you, uh,
Kubayar segera setelah, uh,
fix those holes in the ceiling.
kau perbaiki lubang di langit-langit.
What holes?
Lubang apa?
Gotta go to work. Catch you later, Frank.
Harus kerja. Sampai jumpa, Frank.
Good morning, Vineland!
Selamat pagi, Vineland!
Whoever said that, be quiet, please.
Siapa pun itu, tolong diam.
Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam dalam!
Welcome back.
Selamat datang kembali.
Tonight, it's Jett Fillmore, the vet,
Malam ini, veteran Jett,
taking on Mane Attraction, the champ.
melawan Mane Attraction, juara.
The GOAT debate starts here.
Debat legenda mulai di sini.
Thorns versus Magma.
Thorns lawan Magma.
Go Magma! Go Shivers!
Ayo Magma! Ayo Shivers!
Yeah, go whoever is playing the Thorns. I-I don't care.
Ya, ayo lawan Thorns. Aku tak peduli.
Gerald!
Gerald!
I'm gonna kick you out
Kuusir kau
if you keep wearing the other teams' jerseys.
jika terus pakai jersei tim lawan.
Carol, I'm the ultimate hater.
Carol, aku pembenci sejati.
No pie for you.
Tiada pai untukmu.
Sheep. She took my pie.
Dasar domba. Dia ambil paiku.
The Thorns have broken his heart one too many times.
Thorns telah mematahkan hatinya berkali-kali.
This is Vineland, Gerald.
Ini Vineland, Gerald.
We never give up. We've always got hope.
Kita pantang menyerah. Selalu ada harapan.
The Thorns, they just ne to draft your boy.
Thorns hanya perlu rekrut jagoanmu ini.
I'll turn things around real quick.
Aku akan ubah keadaan dengan cepat.
So, they're drafting delivery goats now?
Jadi, mereka rekrut kambing sekarang?
I need one to deliver food.
Aku butuh 1 untuk antar makanan.
Ooh! About that, Ms. Carol, uh, can I get a raise?
Ooh! Soal itu, Bu Carol, uh, boleh aku naik gaji?
You want a raise?
Kau mau naik gaji?
Tell the Thorns to win a few games
Suruh Thorns menang beberapa laga
so we can get the crowds back in here.
agar penonton kembali ke sini.
I remember when Jett was a rookie.
Aku ingat saat Jett masih pemula.
This place used to be full.
Tempat ini dulu penuh.
Before we realized she was never gonna win us a Claw?
Sebelum kita sadar dia takkan pernah beri kita Claw?
Uh, Carol, can I have my pie back, please?
Uh, Carol, boleh aku minta paiku lagi?
Keep talking. I'll cut you off from ice cream too.
Teruslah bicara. Akan kuhentikan jatah es krimmu juga.
Be careful with these. Oh. Got it.
Hati-hati dengan ini. Oh. Siap.
Oh. Moe needs more coffee,
Oh. Moe butuh kopi lagi,
and the out-of-towners, they want their check.
dan orang luar itu minta tagihan mereka.
How do you always do that? Freaks me out every time.
Bagaimana kau selalu tahu? Selalu buatku ngeri.
Hey, I'm a goat. I see everything.
Hei, aku kambing. Aku melihat segalanya.
Pass it, Will. Okay!
Oper, Will. Oke!
Hey, guys. Got it! See you later, Will!
Hei, kawan. Dapat! Sampai jumpa, Will!
Thorns are already down by 20.
Thorns tertinggal 20 angka.
Oh, come on.
Oh, ayolah.
Up here.
Di atas sini.
All right. Let's do this.
Baiklah. Mari kita mulai.
- Thank you. - I got you.
- Terima kasih. - Sama-sama.
♪ This is the best day Of my life ♪
♪ Ini hari terbaik Dalam hidupku ♪
Step back. Yes!
Mundur. Ya!
- Thank you.
- Terima kasih.
-Here you go. -Appreciate you.
-Ini untukmu. -Terima kasih.
♪ This is the best day Of my life ♪
♪ Ini hari terbaik Dalam hidupku ♪
My mammal. Finally, bro.
Mamaliaku. Akhirnya, Bung.
Chill, Daryl. You ordered a water.
Tenang, Daryl. Kau cuma pesan air.
Water is food too, bro.
Air juga makanan, Bung.
So, Hannah, how's Jett doing?
Jadi, Hannah, bagaimana keadaan Jett?
Mane's kind of working Jett tonight.
Mane sepertinya sedang mempermainkan Jett malam ini.
I hate to say it, she might be washed.
Aku tak ingin mengatakannya, mungkin dia sudah habis masa.
You serious? Jett can handle that one-trick pony.
Kau serius? Jett bisa mengatasi kuda trik-aneh itu.
Um, is his one trick being the best at roarball?
Um, apa trik anehnya menjadi yang terbaik di roarball?
He's got the shooting, the passing...
Tembakannya, operannya...
Picture-perfect pecs.
Otot dada sempurna.
Luxurious locks.
Rambut yang indah.
Mane is pretty much him.
Mane memang jagonya.
Oh, my!
Luar biasa!
Mane Attraction just put... On her head!
Mane Attraction baru saja... Tepat di kepalanya!
...the former number-one pick, Olivia Burke...
...mantan pilihan ke-1, Olivia Burke...
That's not good. ...on a poster.
Itu gawat. ...dipermalukan.
Oh, there's already memes?
Oh, sudah ada memenya?
Oh, "poster child"? Now, that's rough.
Oh, "anak pajangan"? Sadis sekali.
Yeah, that was so not cool.
Ya, itu sama sekali tidak keren.
I'm gonna go train at the Cage.
Aku mau latihan di Cage.
What? You're not gonna watch the game with us?
Apa? Tak mau nonton bersama kami?
Nah, I gotta go while the Cage is empty,
Tidak, aku pergi selagi Cage kosong,
'cause after the game, you know it's gonna fill up.
karena usai laga, pasti akan penuh.
Do not let Grizz catch you.
Jangan sampai Grizz menangkapmu.
Oh, I won't.
Oh, tidak akan.
Roots run deep. Roots run deep.
Akar menghujam. Akar menghujam.
Step back. Jett!
Mundur. Jett!
The crowd goes wild.
Penonton bersorak riuh.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It won't rain on my parade ♪
♪ Semangatku takkan padam ♪
♪ Oh, let it rain, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, biarkanlah, ooh ♪
Another one.
Satu lagi.
With only five seconds left, the ball goes to Harris.
Tersisa 5 detik, bola ke tangan Harris.
He's all alone.
Dia sendirian.
Three, two, one...
3, 2, 1...
What's going on here, folks?
Apa yang terjadi, kawan?
They're resetting the clock?
Mereka atur ulang waktu?
Don't question it.
Jangan tanya.
He's got time for one more shot.
Dia punya waktu untuk 1 tembakan lagi.
Three, two, one...
3, 2, 1...
Roots run deep. Roots run deep. Roots run deep.
Akar menghujam. Akar menghujam. Akar menghujam.
One day, baby. One day.
Suatu hari nanti, Nak. Suatu hari nanti.
Get that weak sauce up out of here.
Enyahkan sampah itu dari sini.
Yo, what's your problem, Grizz?
Yo, apa masalahmu, Grizz?
Every day you're here.
Tiap hari kau ke sini.
Every day I gotta kick you out.
Tiap hari aku harus mengusirmu.
I mean, what are the rules, y'all?
Maksudku, apa aturannya, kawan?
Smalls can't ball.
Si mungil dilarang main.
First off, I'm not a small. I'm a medium.
Pertama, aku bukan mungil. Aku ukuran sedang.
What? Medium fries?
Apa? Kentang goreng sedang?
You will never make it into Roar.
Kau takkan pernah masuk Roar.
I mean, come on. Let me run.
Ayolah. Biar aku tanding.
I'm better than half of y'all anyways.
Aku lebih baik dari setengah kalian.
Let me show you what I got.
Biar kutunjukkan kemampuanku.
Ball me.
Beri bolanya.
Only thing you're running is off this court.
Satu-satunya tandingmu adalah keluar lapangan ini.
Now get out of here.
Sekarang pergi dari sini.
Good night, Shirley. You're in my house now.
Malam, Shirley. Kau ada di rumahku sekarang.
And that's the game.
Laga usai.
Thorns lose by 26.
Thorns kalah telak.
Clock's ticking, Jett.
Waktu berjalan, Jett.
Jett, Jett, Jett, hey, can you sign this for me?
Jett, Jett, Jett, hei, bisa minta tanda tangan?
Of course. Anything for a fan.
Tentu. Apa pun untuk penggemarku.
There you go, kid.
Ini untukmu, Nak.
Thanks, Jett.
Terima kasih, Jett.
Why can't you win a championship?
Kenapa tak bisa juara?
Retire already!
Pensiun saja!
Jett, could we take a photo?
Jett, boleh kami foto?
Jett, third loss in a row.
Jett, kalah ke-3 kalinya.
How does it feel? Flo? Where's Flo?
Gimana rasanya? Flo? Di mana Flo?
When are we gonna stop sucking? Flo!
Kapan kita berhenti kalah? Flo!
Hey. Flo?
Hei. Flo?
Who's seen Flo?
Ada yang lihat Flo?
Hey, there, grumpy cat.
Hei, kucing pemarah.
How'd the game end?
Bagaimana akhir laganya?
I stopped watching
Aku berhenti menonton
and punched myself in the face instead.
dan malah pukul wajahku.
You think this is funny?
Kau pikir ini lucu?
You're the team owner, Flo.
Kau pemilik timnya, Flo.
How am I supposed to win
Bagaimana aku bisa menang
when you've got me surrounded by head cases and has-beens?
jika kau membuatku dikelilingi orang gila dan kedaluwarsa?
Hey, I'm working on it.
Hei, sedang kuusahakan.
We don't even have a sixth player, Flo,
Pemain ke-6 saja tak ada, Flo,
but you got your hooves done.
tapi kuku-kukumu sudah dirias.
Listen here, Jett, free agents aren't free. Okay?
Dengar Jett, pemain bebas transfer tak gratis. Oke?
So unless you have a sixth player in mind
Jadi kecuali jika kau punya ide pemain ke-6
who can fill an arena
yang bisa memenuhi arena
and doesn't want a big, fat check,
dan tidak mau dibayar mahal,
I'm gonna get back to my mud bath, okay?
aku akan kembali mandi lumpur, oke?
Oh, that is hogwash.
Itu omong kosong.
It's your job to figure it out.
Tugasmu untuk mencari tahu.
Trade players, sell the team...
Menukar pemain, menjual tim...
I don't care what you got to do. Just do it. Now.
Terserah kau. Lakukan saja. Sekarang.
Careful what you wish for, Jett.
Hati-hati dengan harapanmu, Jett.
He's fine.
Dia baik-baik saja.
Hey, I'm driving here. Get out of the road, ya medium.
Hei, aku sedang mengemudi. Minggir, dasar orang aneh.
Keep it down. Why are you so loud?
Bisa diam. Kenapa kau berisik?
Hello, William.
Halo, William.
Hey, Frank. How are you?
Hei, Frank. Apa kabar?
Would you happen to have that rent?
Kau punya uang sewa itu?
Oh. Oh, yeah, yeah. Right. Right.
Oh. Oh, ya, ya. Benar. Benar.
Frank, I got you. It's all right here.
Frank, aku bawa. Ini dia.
I meant to give it to you today actually
Sebenarnya aku mau kasih ke kamu hari ini.
22, 23...
22, 23...
This is not actual money, this piece of paper.
Kertas ini bukan uang sungguhan.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ya, ya, ya, ya.
What about last month's and the month before?
Bagaimana dengan bulan lalu dan sebelumnya?
Frank, it's me. Come on.
Frank, ini aku. Ayolah.
I just need a little more time.
Aku butuh waktu sedikit lagi.
You had time, Will.
Kau sudah punya waktu, Will.
I got mouths to feed.
Keluargaku harus makan.
I don't need one more.
Aku tak butuh satu lagi.
-Hey, Will.
-Hei, Will.
-Hey, guys. -Hey, Will. Hey, Will.
-Hei, kawan. -Hei, Will. Hei, Will.
Hey, Will. Hey, Will. Hey, Will.
Hei, Will. Hei, Will. Hei, Will.
Y'all are still awake?
Kalian masih bangun?
-Hey, Will. -Oh, what's up, Theo?
-Hei, Will. -Oh, ada apa, Theo?
Did they let you play at the Cage today?
Mereka mengizinkanmu main di Cage hari ini?
You know me. I'm working on it.
Kau tahu aku. Sedang kuusahakan.
That's a lot of kids.
Anak yang sangat banyak.
Indeed it is.
Memang.
I'm sorry, kiddo.
Maaf, Nak.
Look, get me my rent money by tomorrow
Dengar, bayar uang sewanya besok
or I gotta rent the room to somebody else.
atau akan kusewakan ke orang lain.
Capisce?
Mengerti?
Will, I forgot to tell you--
Will, aku lupa beritahu--
Hey, kids, come on. Get in the tub.
Ayo, anak-anak. Masuk ke bak mandi.
Here we go, here we go.
Ayo, masuk, masuk.
You need money? Well, you're in luck
MULAI DENGAN BIG-BRONCO-CRYPTO
'cause you can start earning up to 300 bucks per day.
karena kau bisa dapat 300 dolar sehari.
How? By trading crypto on BigBroncoCrypto...
Caranya? Perdagangkan kripto di BigBroncoCrypto...
Frank, I'm pregnant again.
Frank, aku hamil lagi.
That's amazing, sweetheart.
Itu luar biasa, Sayang.
Hey, Will...
Hei, Will...
...gonna need that rent money.
...aku butuh uang sewa itu.
Boom!
Bum!
Check these out.
Lihat ini.
Vineland green, Fillmore Fours, in the flesh.
Vineland hijau, Fillmore Fours, langsung di depanmu.
Jett wore these in the Furball game.
Jett pakai ini di laga Furball.
Normally, these sell for around six...
Biasanya dijual sekitar 600...
...but I'll give it to you
...tapi kuberi kau harga
for five.
500.
No, not the Fours.
Bukan, jangan sepatu itu.
Oh, I wanted those.
Oh, aku menginginkannya.
But you're broke.
Tapi kau sedang miskin.
But if I had the Fours I wouldn't look it.
Tapi kalau kupakai Fours, aku takkan terlihat begitu.
Ah. Yes. Yes, you would. It's gonna be okay.
Ah. Ya. Ya, benar. Semua akan baik saja.
Pristine upper mesh. Taut laces.
Jaring atas murni. Tali yang kencang.
Mmm.
Mmm.
- Nutty. - Nasty.
- Edan. - Gila.
250.
250.
Come on. 250? How dare you.
Ayolah. 250? Tega nian.
The disrespect.
Tidak sopan.
Come on, Will. I can do installments.
Ayolah, Will. Aku bisa mencicilnya.
Yeah, that's great, Dary but my landlord can't.
Ide bagus, Dary, tapi pemilik rumahku tidak bisa.
I can't watch this.
Tak tahan melihatnya.
So, 400?
Jadi, 400?
240. I-It's going down?
240. T-Turun lagi?
230. Dang, stop!
230. Sial, hentikan!
Please, please!
Kumohon!
Yo! No way!
Yo! Gila!
Y'all are not gonna believe this.
Kalian takkan percaya ini.
Mane is at the Cage,
Mane ada di Cage,
and he's taking on all challengers.
dan dia menantang siapa pun.
So, we, uh, doing this or what?
Jadi, kita akan ke sana atau bagaimana?
Okay, fine.
Oke, baiklah.
All right. Let's dip.
Ayo meluncur.
Who's got next?
Giliran siapa?
♪ No, nobody can Do it like me ♪
♪ Tiada yang bisa Melakukannya sepertiku ♪
♪ Zoo Pals plate With the Kid Cuisine ♪
♪ Piring Zoo Pals Dengan Kid Cuisine ♪
Now watch this.
Lihat ini.
Give me that.
Berikan padaku.
♪ 360s in my green machine ♪
♪ Rotasi 360 di mesin hijauku ♪
Garbage.
Sampah.
I said, who's got next?
Kubilang, giliran siapa?
I can't hear nothing. Where y'all at?
Tidak ada yang menyahut. Mana kalian?
Who got next?
Giliran siapa?
Hey, yo. Check ball.
Hei, yo. Periksa bola.
Yeah!
Ya!
Get him, Grizz!
Habisi, Grizz!
Got a piece of flaming garbage over here.
Ada secuil sampah di sini.
Touch me. Touch me.
Sentuh aku. Sentuh aku.
Get lost, Mane, you're a bum.
Enyah, Mane, kau pecundang.
Seriously? You mean to tell me
Serius? Ingin bilang padaku
this is the best Vineland's got?
ini yang terbaik dari Vineland?
I thought the Cage is where roarball was born.
Kukira di Cage bola raung ini lahir.
I guess this town's only as weak as its greatest player.
Kukira kota ini sama lemahnya dengan pemain terbaiknya.
Hey, where she at?
Hei, di mana dia?
If Jett's nowhere to be found, then somebody gotta answer me.
Jika Jett tak ada, seseorang harus menjawabku.
- Who's got next? - I got next.
- Giliran siapa? - Aku.
Who said that?
Siapa bilang?
Hey!
Hei!
Excuse me. Pardon. Hey, move out the way.
Permisi. Maaf. Hei, minggir.
I got next.
Giliranku.
Check up.
Periksa.
Wait, wait, a goat?
Tunggu, kambing?
Thank you for the laugh, little dude,
Terima kasih leluconnya, Kawan mungil,
but, uh, why don't you just run on back
tapi kenapa tidak kembali sana
to the kiddie pool or something.
ke kolam renang anak-anak atau apalah.
Get you an ice cream.
Beli es krim.
But, seriously, any takers?
Tapi, serius, ada penantang?
Even if I put money on it?
Bahkan jika kupertaruhkan uang?
First the shoes, now your rent money?
Pertama sepatu, sekarang uang sewamu?
Yes, Will. Commit.
Ya, Will. Berkomitmenlah.
Oh, Mane, what are you gonna do now?
Oh, Mane, mau apa kau sekarang?
Where's all the big talk now, Mane?
Mana omong besarmu sekarang, Mane?
Let's go, Vineland!
Maju, Vineland!
Oh. So this is all the gre Vineland has to offer?
Oh. Jadi cuma ini yang terbaik dari Vineland?
A goat and some spare change?
Seekor kambing dan uang receh?
But you know what?
Tapi asal tahu saja.
Mane doesn't duck smoke so check up.
Mane tak pernah menolak. Ayo.
Let's do it.
Lakukanlah.
Everything counts as one.
Semuanya dihitung 1.
First to three.
Siapa mencapai 3 dulu.
Your ball.
Bolamu.
- Oh, snap! - That's one.
- Oh, gila! - Itu yang pertama.
I'd fight a big for that.
Aku akan bertarung besar.
Oh. So you do know how to pass.
Oh. Jadi kau bisa mengoper.
You gonna guard me from all the way out there?
Akan kau mengawalku dari sana?
Let's go.
Ayo.
Come on.
Maju.
When I get that ball, it's over.
Saat kurebut bola itu, usai sudah.
Whoa!
Wah!
You got owned by a goat!
Kau dikalahkan kambing!
-Oh, shoot! -Hey!
-Oh, tembak! -Hei!
This goat out here!
Kambing ini ada di sini!
This dude's eating beans!
Orang ini makan kacang!
All right. Let's get serious.
Baiklah. Mari serius.
Looks like you're gonna make me take my chains off.
Sepertinya kau memaksaku melepaskan kalungku.
Yeah, man. Take it all off.
Ya, kawan. Lepas semua.
Oh, okay. I see.
Oh, oke. Paham.
You're an outside shooter, huh?
Kau penembak jarak jauh, ya?
Now get past me.
Coba lewati aku.
Oh.
Oh.
Now we playing for real.
Sekarang kita main sungguhan.
This is how it feel in the league.
Beginilah rasanya di liga.
This is my house.
Ini kandangku.
You're mine now.
Kau milikku sekarang.
Boom!
Bum!
Boom shakalaka!
Bum shakalaka!
Ooh.
Ooh.
Fool, I wasn't helping you up.
Bodoh, aku tak membantumu.
I just wanted my cash.
Aku cuma mau uangku.
Thanks.
Terima kasih.
Hey! We got goat money.
Hei! Kita dapat uangnya.
That wasn't bad.
Tak buruk juga.
Everyone didn't have their phones out for that long.
Orang-orang merekam itu cukup lama.
Right, Daryl?
Benar, Daryl?
Yes, they did.
Ya, benar.
Come on. Come on.
Ayolah. Ayolah.
What?
Apa?
I respect that.
Aku menghargainya.
Hey, Will.
Hei, Will.
Will, uh, I'm really sorry about my dad.
Will, uh, maafkan perilaku Ayahku.
But I want you to know I believe in you.
Tapi ketahuilah bahwa aku memercayaimu.
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh!
And I made you a sandwich. Catch!
Kubuatkan roti. Tangkap!
Oops. Airball.
Oops. Meleset.
Sorry about that.
Maaf soal itu.
I'll still see you at the Greenhouse
Sampai jumpa di Greenhouse
when you're playing for the Thorns!
saat kau bermain untuk Thorns!
Thanks, Theo. Good luck!
Terima kasih, Theo. Semoga beruntung!
Yo, I told you that video was crazy.
Yo, sudah kubilang video itu gila.
Yeah, that dude was guzzling.
Ya, dia melahapnya.
- Yo! What's up, my mammal? - Hey.
- Yo! Apa kabar, Sob? - Hei.
- Oh, hey. - There he is.
- Oh, hei. - Itu dia.
Thanks for letting me crash at your place.
Terima kasih tumpangannya di tempatmu.
You brought your stuff? Hey, throw it on the pile.
Bawa barangmu? Lempar saja ke tumpukan itu.
Still haven't cleaned.
Belum kubersihkan.
Okay, just pick a pile. They're all filthy.
Pilih saja satu. Semuanya kotor.
Now quit your yapping and come check out
Berhenti mengoceh dan ayo lihat
what I've been cooking up.
apa yang kusiapkan.
Will wins!
Will menang!
Oh, you like that?
Oh, kau suka itu?
Come on, this is gonna go viral.
Ayolah, ini akan viral.
You broke his ankles.
Kau mengecohnya habis-habisan.
Yeah, and he broke my horn.
Ya, dan dia mematahkan tandukku.
Ugh. Will, look,
Ugh. Will, dengar,
you wanted footage of you playing against big
kau ingin rekaman saat melawan pemain besar.
And you just went up against
Dan kau baru saja melawan
the biggest, baddest in all of roarball.
pemain terbesar dan terhebat di bola raung.
Yep, yep. Facts. You did that, Will.
Ya. Fakta. Kau berhasil, Will.
Well, I'm just gonna make this one live
Akan segera kusiarkan secara langsung
'cause I think Daryl just farted. Ugh.
karena Daryl baru saja kentut. Ugh.
I'll see you both later.
Sampai jumpa nanti.
- I got a date. Need to shave. - Ooh!
- Aku ada janji. Mau cukuran. - Ooh!
With who?
Dengan siapa?
Oh, I didn't tell you? Your mom.
Oh, belum kubilang? Ibumu.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, sial.
Yeah, she got you, bro.
Ya, kau kena, Bung.
Okay, okay. Wasn't even funny.
Oke, oke. Tidak lucu.
Hey, bro. Wanna play some Roar 2K?
Hei, Bung. Mau main Roar 2K?
Nah, think I'm good.
Tidak, aku lelah.
Should probably call it a night, you know?
Sebaiknya aku istirahat, mengerti?
No, sure thing. Yeah, make yourself comfortable.
Tentu. Anggap rumah sendiri.
I'm gonna get on these sticks.
Aku akan main stik dulu.
Okay.
Oke.
Ugh.
Ugh.
It's him, look.
Itu dia, lihat.
Hey! What's up, buddy?
Hei! Apa kabar, Kawan?
Hey, Will.
Hei, Will.
-Hey, Will. -Hi, anonymous animal.
-Hei, Will. -Hai, hewan anonim.
Look, Mom. It's Will.
Lihat, Bu. Itu Will.
-I'm sorry. -That's okay. It's okay.
-Maafkan aku. -Tak apa. Tak apa.
Yo, who is the clown that parked like that outside?
Siapa orang bodoh yang parkir sembarangan di luar?
Everybody good?
Semua baik-baik saja?
Why are y'all not blinking?
Kenapa kalian tidak berkedip?
That's me, sweetheart. I'm the clown.
Itu aku, Sayang. Aku pelakunya.
You're Florence Everson!
Kau Florence Everson!
You're the owner of the Thorns!
Kau pemilik Thorns!
You can ignore all the voicemails, Mr. Harris.
Abaikan semua pesan suara, Pak Harris.
It looks like I found you myself.
Sepertinya kutemukan kau sendiri.
She's been waiting for you.
Dia sudah menunggumu.
Without ordering anything.
Tanpa memesan apa pun.
Sit.
Duduk.
You had quite the game yesterday.
Permainanmu hebat kemarin.
You broke Mane's ankles so hard,
Kau mengecoh Mane begitu keras,
I thought they were gonna have to put him down!
kukira mereka akan menjatuhkannya!
And the Internet just loved it.
Dan internet menyukai itu.
They love you.
Mereka menyukaimu.
Yo! That's crazy!
Yo! Itu gila!
Oh, it gets crazier.
Oh, akan lebih gila lagi.
Will, maybe you haven't noticed,
Will, mungkin kau belum sadar,
but the team is awful.
tapi tim ini payah.
Oh, no. We trash.
Oh, tidak. Kami sampah.
We have the league's best player
Kami punya pemain terbaik liga
and no path to the Claw, again...
dan tak ada jalan menuju trofi, lagi...
Small to small, I believe you are exactly
Sesama orang kecil, aku percaya kau adalah
what Jett and this team needs right now.
yang Jett dan tim ini butuhkan sekarang.
Goat, sure.
Kambing, tentu saja.
But I think you might be a two-horned unicorn.
Tapi menurutku kau mungkin keajaiban langka.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Benarkah? - Ya.
I'd like to make you an offer.
Aku ingin beri tawaran.
We need a sixth player
Kami butuh pemain ke-6
to join the Thorns for the back half of the seaso
untuk bergabung di Thorns pada paruh musim ini.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, Tuhan.
Is it really-- Is it finally happening?
Apakah ini benar-- Akhirnya terjadi?
I just need you to sign here, some initials here,
Tanda tangan di sini, paraf di sini,
and you're officially a Thorn.
dan kau resmi jadi anggota.
And, uh, Jett. She signed off on this?
Dan, uh, Jett. Dia setuju dengan ini?
In many ways, it was her idea. Yeah.
Dalam banyak hal, ini adalah idenya. Ya.
So what's it gonna be?
Jadi bagaimana?
Play for Vineland, or stay here and bus my table?
Main untuk Vineland, atau tetap di sini membereskan meja?
Pen. Pen! Pen. Someone give me a pen!
Pena. Pena! Pena. Tolong beri aku pena!
I don't have a-- Ow!
Aku tak punya-- Aw!
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
W. H.
W. H.
Where there's a Will, there's a way.
Di mana ada kemauan (Will), di situ ada jalan.
Oh, congratulations, sweetie. We're so proud of you.
Oh, selamat, Sayang. Kami sangat bangga.
Will! Will! Will! Will! Will!
Will! Will! Will! Will! Will!
I cannot believe it!
Sulit kupercaya!
I'm gonna be a Vineland Thorn!
Aku akan jadi pemain Thorns!
-Breaking news! -You're not gonna believe it!
-Berita sela! -Kalian takkan percaya ini!
-Will, it went viral! -It certainly did.
-Will, kau viral! -Tentu saja.
I'm so excited, Will.
Aku girang sekali, Will.
Who's the fancy pig?
Siapa babi menor itu?
I hate this town.
Aku benci kota ini.
Oh. It hurts. It hurts.
Oh. Sakit. Sakit.
Welcome to the Roar Roundup.
Selamat datang di Roar Roundup.
I'm two-time champion, Chuck,
Aku Chuck juara ganda,
alongside my cohost, itty-bitty-bitey-buddy,
bersama rekan siaranku, si kecil tukang gigit,
Rusty. Rusty!
Rusty. Rusty!
I can't wait till they put you out to pasture, Chuck.
Tak sabar melihatmu dibuang ke padang rumput, Chuck.
Well, but back to the question we ask every season.
Kembali ke pertanyaan yang kita ajukan tiap musim.
Can you be the GOAT without winning a championship?
Bisa jadi legenda sejati tanpa meraih gelar juara?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, ya.
- Claws make careers. - What is that?
- Trofilah yang membentuk karier. - Apa itu?
- You don't say! - Nuh-uh.
- Jangan bilang begitu! - Tidak.
I feel for Fillmore. She's always been a great player,
Kasihan Fillmore. Dia selalu jadi pemain hebat,
but Father Time catches up with everyone.
tapi waktu akan mengejar semua orang.
Without me, they wouldn't have anything to talk about.
Tanpaku, mereka tak punya bahan obrolan.
All stats, no Claws.
Penuh rekor, tanpa gelar.
But you can't put all the blame on her.
Tapi tak bisa timpakan semua salah padanya.
Anyone who's watched this team
Siapa pun yang menonton tim ini
and thinks Jett's the biggest problem is blind as a--
dan anggap Jett masalah utamanya berarti buta seperti--
Blind as a what, Chuck? Say it. Blind as a what?
Buta seperti apa, Chuck? Katakan. Buta seperti apa?
I am the all-time leading scorer in Roar history.
Aku pencetak poin terbanyak sepanjang sejarah Roar.
Speaking of the Thorns,
Bicara soal Thorns,
we've got some breaking news, Chuck!
kita punya berita terbaru, Chuck!
The Vineland Thorns have finally signed a sixth player.
Thorns akhirnya merekrut pemain ke-6 mereka.
Looks like they're finally getting Jett some help.
Sepertinya Jett akhirnya dapat bantuan.
Yes! A crocodile?
Ya! Seekor buaya?
No, no, no, no. Bigger. A gorilla?
Bukan, bukan, bukan. Lebih besar. Gorila?
We go now to owner Florence Everson...
Kita sapa sekarang, pemilik Florence Everson...
That's what I'm talking about.
Itu baru benar.
...with an exclusive interview.
...dalam wawancara eksklusif.
We signed roarball's first small.
Kami merekrut si mungil pertama di bola raung.
A small what?
Si mungil apa?
We got a little...
Kami dapat yang kecil...
A little, uh, what?
Yang kecil, uh, apa?
-...teeny... -A what now?
-...mungil... -Apa lagi sekarang?
-...tiny... -Come again.
-...imut... -Ulangi lagi.
...goat.
...kambing.
A goat?
Kambing?
Oh, not again.
Oh, jangan lagi.
Florence Marjorie Everson!
Florence Marjorie Everson!
You're signing a goat? Have you lost your mind?
Kau rekrut kambing? Kau gila?
Okay. Excuse me.
Oke. Permisi.
You're the one who asked for a team who could win the Claw
Kau yang minta tim yang bisa menangkan trofi
and you didn't care how. Remember?
dan kau tak peduli caranya. Ingat?
Well, I care about this.
Aku peduli soal ini.
I can't play with a goat.
Aku tak bisa main dengan kambing.
He's an embarrassment to the team.
Dia cuma aib bagi tim ini.
to the city. He's a--
Dia aib bagi kota ini. Dia--
Uh... He's sitting right there.
Uh... Dia duduk tepat di sana.
Hey!
Hei!
You gotta be kidding me.
Pasti kau bercanda.
I couldn't even see him in the chair, Flo.
Aku bahkan tak melihatnya, Flo.
How am I supposed to see him on the court?
Bagaimana aku bisa melihatnya di lapangan nanti?
I'll be the goat in the Thorns jersey.
Akan ada kambing dalam jersei Thorns.
You feel me?
Kau mengerti maksudku?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Look away, Flo. I'm just gonna eat him.
Palingkan wajahmu, Flo. Aku akan memakannya.
Yeah, I'm gonna eat him with a side of ranch dressing,
Ya, aku akan memakannya dengan saus peternakan,
and we're gonna act like none of this happened.
dan kita akan bertingkah seolah ini tak terjadi.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I do not taste good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Rasaku tidak enak.
I-I thought you said she knew.
K-Kupikir kau bilang dia sudah tahu.
It's my job to bend the truth, Will. Come on.
Tugasku untuk membengkokkan fakta, Will. Ayolah.
It's also my job to play the long game.
Tugasku juga untuk memainkan taktik jangka panjang.
This is generating more attention
Ini menghasilkan lebih banyak atensi
than we have had in years.
dibanding tahun-tahun sebelumnya.
You don't want him on the court, that's your call.
Kau tak mau dia di lapangan, itu terserahmu.
But he stays on the roster.
Tapi dia tetap masuk dalam tim.
Oh, you must have lost your mind.
Oh, kau pasti sudah gila.
Put your paw down.
Turunkan cakarmu.
You should be elated.
Seharusnya kau senang.
The stars have aligned perfectly
Bintang-bintang telah sejajar dengan sempurna
because the press is dying to meet Will.
karena media sekarat ingin bertemu Will.
Will, down. Get down.
Will, turun. Cepat turun.
Oh, okay.
Oh, oke.
And I want you to introduce him.
Dan aku ingin kau memperkenalkannya.
No. Not happening. Yes, you are.
Tidak. Tak akan terjadi. Ya, harus.
They're actually waiting for you right downstairs.
Mereka sedang menunggu kalian di bawah.
So keep them tails up high, yes?
Jadi tetap angkat ekornya, ya?
Big smiles! Love you both! Now get out!
Senyum lebar! Aku sayang kalian! Sekarang pergi!
Jett, hey.
Jett, hei.
I just wanted you to know, this is my dream come true.
Ketahuilah, ini mimpiku jadi nyata.
I mean, to play with you, like, my favorite player of all time.
Maksudku, main bersamamu, pemain favoritku sepanjang masa.
I know I'm not what you expected,
Aku tahu aku bukan yang kau harapkan,
but I've spent my whole life training for this moment.
tapi aku berlatih seumur hidupku untuk momen ini.
And if you just give me a sho--
Dan jika kau beri aku ke--
Look, kid. I saw your little viral video.
Dengar, Nak. Aku lihat video viral konyolmu.
Mane baked you like a birthday cake.
Mane memanggangmu seperti kue ulang tahun.
Yeah, yeah, no. I'm gonna enjoy
Ya, ya, tidak. Aku akan nikmati tontonan
watching the piranhas eat you alive.
piranha memangsamu hidup-hidup.
-Will! Will! -Will, over here!
-Will! Will! -Will, di sini!
-Will!
-Will!
-Will, Will, Will!
-Will, Will, Will!
Do you think going viral in a playground entitles you
Apakah kau pikir viral di lapangan itu berhak
to play professional roarball?
membuatmu bermain bola raung pro?
Do you worry you'll let other smalls down?
Apa kau khawatir akan mengecewakan kaum kecil lainnya?
Aren't you just a shameless publicity stunt
Tidakkah kau ini cuma pemeran pengganti tak tahu malu
to distract from another Thorns losing season?
untuk mengalihkan perhatian dari kekalahan Thorns musim ini?
Are you actually a goat?
Kau benar-benar kambing?
Don't you just kinda suck?
Bukankah kau cuma orang payah?
I... Sorry. Can-- Can you repeat the questio
Aku... Maaf. Bisa-- Bisa ulangi pertanyaannya?
Hey, hey. One at a time, y'all.
Hei, hei. Satu per satu, kawan.
This boy is not even media trained, okay?
Bocah ini bahkan tak terlatih menghadapi media, oke?
So, Will. How does it feel to be the first small ever
Jadi, Will. Bagaimana rasanya jadi si mungil pertama
to sign a professional roarball contract?
yang tanda menangani kontrak bola raung pro?
Uh, to be honest with you, it's all kinda surreal.
Uh, sejujurnya, ini semua seperti mimpi.
I mean, last night I was fighting off roaches
Maksudku, semalam aku mengusir kecoak
at my best friend's crib...
di rumah sahabatku...
...and now I'm playing for the Thorns.
...dan sekarang aku bermain untuk Thorns.
You shouldn't have said that.
Tak seharusnya kau bilang itu.
Will, we are getting word that the roach community
Will, kami dapat kabar bahwa komunitas kecoak
was pretty offended by your last comment.
cukup tersinggung dengan komentarmu tadi.
Would you care to issue an apology?
Maukah kau meminta maaf?
Oh, gosh. No, no, no, no. That's not what I meant.
Oh, Tuhan. Tidak, tidak. Bukan itu maksudku.
I love roaches. Lies.
Aku suka kecoak. Bohong.
-Can we, uh, move on to the next question? -Up here.
-Bisa kita, uh, lanjut ke pertanyaan berikutnya? -Di sini.
So, Will, you're not at all concerned about being hurt?
Jadi, Will, kau tak khawatir terluka sama sekali?
Roarball takes its toll on the toughest of bigs.
Bola raung menuntut pengorbanan dari pemain besar paling tangguh.
I imagine for a small,
Kupikir bagi si mungil,
it could be fatal.
bisa berakibat fatal.
Uh, well... No, no. Will knows the risks.
Uh, ya... Tidak, tidak. Will tahu risikonya.
Could he be clobbered? Possibly.
Bisa dipukul? Mungkin.
Crushed? Perhaps.
Dihancurkan? Mungkin.
Killed? Probably.
Terbunuh? Mungkin.
But that's how much he loves the game.
Tapi sebesar itulah dia cinta permainan ini.
He'd die for it.
Dia rela mati demi ini.
Right, Will? Right.
Benar, Will? Benar.
What about Mane?
Bagaimana dengan Mane?
Are you worried about a rematch down the line?
Apa kau khawatirkan laga ulang nanti?
No. No way.
Tidak. Mustahil.
We call this dude the horse whisperer,
Kami memanggilnya pembisik kuda,
'cause he broke that bronco's back, okay?
karena dia mematahkan punggung kuda itu, oke?
You know what he was telling me earlier?
Kau tahu apa yang dia katakan padaku sebelumnya?
He's got a nickname for Mane.
Dia punya julukan untuk Mane.
He calls him "My Little Pony."
Dia memanggilnya "Kuda Poni Kecilku."
Don't you? No, I didn't say that.
Bukankah begitu? Tidak, aku tak bilang begitu.
You do. I did not say that.
Kau bilang begitu. Aku tidak mengatakannya.
And he also said that Mane
Dan dia juga bilang Mane
definitely ain't the GOAT,
jelas bukan legenda,
and his hair is wack, too, which I also agree with.
dan rambutnya juga aneh, yang aku setujui.
Oh, he's dead.
Oh, dia tamat.
- Why are you doing this to me? - Last question.
- Kenapa kau lakukan ini padaku? - Pertanyaan terakhir.
Uh, this one's for Jett. You're in year fifteen.
Uh, ini untuk Jett. Kau di tahun ke-15.
The team's bringing on a goat to solve its problems.
Tim merekrut kambing untuk selesaikan masalahnya.
Do you ever wonder if it's time to hang it up?
Pernahkah kau berpikir inilah saatnya untuk pensiun?
I'm not hanging up anything, okay?
Aku tidak akan pensiun, oke?
I feel great right now,
Aku merasa hebat sekarang,
playing some of the best ball of my career.
memainkan bola terbaikku di sepanjang karierku.
And please, I've played with every mutt
Dan tolong, aku pernah bermain dengan semua orang buangan
this league has to offer.
yang ditawarkan liga ini.
My only concern is going out there
Kekhawatiran utamaku adalah pergi ke sana
and doing what I gotta do to win the Claw,
dan lakukan apa yang harus kulakukan untuk menangkan Claw,
and nothing, and I mean nothing,
dan tak ada, dan maksudku tak ada,
is gonna get in the way of that.
yang akan menghalanginya.
Thank you. Bagels on the third floor.
Terima kasih. Bagel di lantai 3.
Jett, over here!
Jett, di sini!
Yeah. Uh, cool.
Ya. Uh, keren.
Do you have any comment?
Punya komentar?
I can-- Okay, thank you.
Bisa aku-- Oke, terima kasih.
Bye.
Sampai jumpa.
Coach Dennis, how do you plan
Pelatih Dennis, bagaimana rencanamu
on utilizing the goat in the rotation?
manfaatkan kambing ini dalam rotasi?
That's a great question. Well--
Itu pertanyaan bagus. Ya--
Dennis, he's all yours.
Dennis, dia milikmu sekarang.
Hey, Jett, you got a second?
Hei, Jett, punya waktu sebentar?
I just wanted to go over these new plays.
Aku cuma ingin bahas taktik baru ini.
You heard me. Uh, we'll do it later.
Kau dengar aku. Uh, nanti saja kita bahas.
How you doing, kid? Dennis Cooper.
Apa kabar, Nak? Dennis Cooper.
Pleased to meet you.
Senang bertemu denganmu.
Oh, I know you, Coach Dennis.
Oh, aku kenal kau, Pelatih Dennis.
It's an honor.
Ini suatu kehormatan.
Coach is a strong word.
Pelatih itu panggilan terlalu kuat.
I'm more of an underpaid clipboard stand.
Aku lebih seperti penyangga papan klip bergaji rendah.
But I keep trying.
Tapi aku terus berusaha.
Uh, let's get you suited up for the game.
Uh, ayo persiapkan dirimu untuk pertandingan.
I'm ready to play.
Aku siap bermain.
Play? I... That's cute. No.
Bermain? Aku... Manis sekali. Tidak.
What? Nothing.
Apa? Bukan apa-apa.
And here we are.
Dan kita sampai.
No way. The Thorns locker room?
Mustahil. Ruang ganti Thorns?
Get dressed and come meet the team.
Berpakaianlah dan kenalan dengan tim.
This is crazy!
Ini gila!
Yo! My name. On a Thorns jersey.
Yo! Namaku. Di jersei Thorns.
Oh, wait. Fillmore 13's?
Oh, tunggu. Sepatu Fillmore 13?
Not bad.
Lumayan.
Right?
Benar 'kan?
It's game night.
Ini malam pertandingan.
Welcome back to Regionally Organized Animal Roarball.
Selamat datang di Regional Organized Animal Roarball.
The sport with the wildest courts.
Olahraga dengan lapangan paling liar.
Stalactites.
Stalaktit.
Sandstorms.
Badai pasir.
Cliffs.
Tebing.
Ice.
Es.
Fire. And vines!
Api. Dan tanaman rambat!
Tonight, we're at the Greenhouse,
Malam ini, kita di Greenhouse,
and the stadium is rocking
dan stadion bergoyang
for the first of three straight home games.
untuk laga kandang pertama dari 3 pertandingan beruntun.
And no surprise, the smalls have shown up big
Tak heran, banyak si mungil hadir untuk
for Vineland's newest Thorn.
pemain baru Thorns.
Somebunny's in love!
Ada kelinci yang kasmaran!
Looks like they're necking!
Sepertinya mereka bermesraan!
"Polly want a cracker?" Am I right, up-Chuck?
"Burung beo mau biskuit?" Benar, 'kan, Chuck?
Oh, you caught it!
Oh, kau menangkapnya!
I'm a genius.
Aku jenius.
Okay, Olivia. Clear your mind.
Oke, Olivia. Jernihkan pikiranmu.
I am in control.
Aku pegang kendali.
I know who I am. I am good enough.
Aku tahu siapa diriku. Aku cukup baik.
I do not care about the opinions of others.
Aku tak peduli pendapat orang lain.
I do not care what they're saying about me online,
Aku tak peduli apa yang mereka katakan di internet,
right now, across multiple platforms which I could check,
sekarang ini, di berbagai platform yang bisa kuperiksa,
just to see what they're saying.
hanya untuk tahu apa yang mereka katakan.
Phone! Phone. Does anyone have a phone?
Ponsel! Ponsel. Ada yang punya ponsel?
You're not even in uniform!
Kau bahkan belum memakai seragam!
Ha! It's tear-away.
Ha! Bisa dilepas.
Oh, Lenny. We're gonna get you!
Oh, Lenny. Kami akan menangkapmu!
Listen. I celebrate your creativity with the foam,
Dengar. Ayah hargai kreativitasmu dengan busa itu,
but it's not okay to shoot Daddy in the face, okay? Great.
tapi jangan tembak wajah Ayah, oke? Bagus.
Cute kids.
Anak yang manis.
Yeah, I know. Right?
Ya, aku tahu. Benar?
with a weird smile on his face.
dengan senyum aneh di wajahnya.
Uh, I'm Will Harris.
Uh, aku Will Harris.
Ready to help the team win however I can.
Siap membantu tim menang bagaimana pun caranya.
Oh, look, a pre-game snack.
Oh, lihat, camilan pralaga.
Let me just unhinge my jaw.
Biar kubuka rahangku.
Please, please! No! Don't eat me! Don't eat me!
Kumohon, jangan! Jangan makan! Jangan kau makan!
It's the viral kid! He's sick?
Dia bocah viral! Dia sakit?
No, he went viral.
Tidak, dia viral.
Weird. I like it. Come. Dance.
Aneh. Aku suka. Ayo. Menari.
We're not doing your little dance, Modo.
Kami takkan menari tarianmu, Modo.
I kinda like it.
Aku menyukainya.
Don't let them control you.
Jangan biarkan mereka mengendalikanmu.
It's really loud in here, right?
Di sini bising sekali, ya?
Hey, Jett? Do you think I'll get some playing time tonight?
Hei, Jett? Apa aku bisa main malam ini?
Introducing your newest Thorn.
Inilah pemain baru Thorns.
Coming in at a hot 5'7"...
Tingginya 170 sentimeter...
...from South Vineland,
...dari Vineland Selatan,
the Mane-slayer himself, Will Harris!
pembunuh Mane, Will Harris!
Where'd he go? I can't see him.
Ke mana dia pergi? Tak kulihat.
Will history be made tonight,
Akankah sejarah tercipta malam ini,
or will he follow in your underwhelming footsteps, Chuck?
atau ikuti jejakmu yang mengecewakan, Chuck?
You suck, Rusty. And yes, that was a bat joke.
Kau payah, Rusty. Dan ya, itu lelucon soal kelelawar.
Yeah! Let's go, Will! Yeah, Will!
Ya! Ayo, Will! Ya, Will!
That's Will, right? He kind of looks like a gerbil.
Itu Will, 'kan? Mirip tikus gurun.
Do you think Will's gonna play?
Kira-kira Will akan main?
I hope not, or we're gonna watch that kid die on live TV.
Kuharap tidak, karena kita bisa lihat dia mati di TV nasional.
Gerald!
Gerald!
-Great! Yes! There it is! -Let's go, baby! Keep it up!
-Bagus! Ya! Itu dia! -Ayo, Sayang! Teruskan!
Hey, Coach, when do you think I might get in?
Hei, Pelatih, kapan kira-kira aku dimasukkan?
-Just study the playbook, kid. -End his bloodline!
-Pelajari saja taktiknya, Nak. -Akhiri keturunannya!
Oh, story time?
Oh, mau didongengi?
Yeah. Bring it in. Once, there was a play called Eagle 24.
Ya. Kumpul. Alkisah, ada taktik bernama Rajawali 24.
Oh, I like this one.
Oh, aku suka ini.
Anyone tired? I could sub in.
Ada yang capek? Aku bisa ganti.
-I could take a break. -No.
-Aku mau istirahat. -Tidak.
He's gonna be playing in the next game. Trust me.
Dia akan main di laga selanjutnya. Percayalah.
We need a bucket here.
Kita butuh angka sekarang.
Modo, hang out on the perimeter. Space the floor.
Modo, berjaga di area pinggir. Beri jarak di lapangan.
Do your thing.
Lakukan tugasmu.
I always do.
Aku selalu melakukannya.
Ball! Ball!
Bola! Bola!
Ball! Ball! Ball! Ball!
Bola! Bola! Bola! Bola!
Hey, I actually noticed that the moose always drives right,
Hei, aku perhatikan rusa besar itu selalu menusuk ke kanan,
so if you just shift the defense a li--
jadi jika kau ubah sedikit arah pertahanan--
Who wants an acacia leaf break?
Siapa mau rehat daun akasia?
Ooh, ooh. I do!
Ooh, ooh. Aku mau!
Tomorrow, history will be made.
Besok, sejarah akan terukir.
And I mean it this time.
Dan kali ini aku serius.
Shake it off, Archie!
Lupakan itu, Archie!
I got water, towels, emotional support.
Bawa air, handuk, dukungan moral.
I'm covered.
Semua sudah siap.
And now they'll hit the road with a goat
Dan kini mereka akan tandang bersama kambing
who's yet to see a dime of playing time.
yang belum pernah bermain sama sekali.
Ouch. Ooh.
Aduh. Ooh.
No days off, am I right?
Tiada hari libur, 'kan?
No, no, no. Nope.
Tidak, tidak. Tidak.
This is a private practice session.
Ini adalah sesi latihan pribadi.
Hey, watch this. From the logo. Nothing but net.
Hei, lihat ini. Dari logo. Masuk mulus.
Hmm. Lucky shot.
Hmm. Cuma beruntung.
Hmm. Maybe.
Hmm. Mungkin.
Bank shot.
Pantul papan.
I'm feeling good today.
Aku merasa hebat hari ini.
I want some playing time.
Aku ingin waktu bermain.
Not happening.
Tak akan terjadi.
Let's shoot for it.
Mari bertanding.
Or are you scared you're gonna lose to a goa
Atau kau takut kalah dari seekor kambing?
Top of the stands, hook shot off the glass,
Puncak tribun, tembakan kait pantul,
spin around the rim, in.
putar jaring, masuk.
Jett from downtown. Did it.
Jett dari area tiga angka. Berhasil.
Easy.
Mudah.
Through the vines, in.
Lewat tanaman rambat, masuk.
Yeah, baby!
Ya, Sayang!
What else you got?
Apa lagi yang kau bisa?
Off the top,
Dari atas,
in.
masuk.
Ooh.
Ooh.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Hanging from the lights.
Menggantung di lampu.
Easy.
Mudah.
Ooh!
Ooh!
You are mine now.
Kau milikku sekarang.
From the tunnel, over the backboard,
Dari terowongan, lewat belakang papan,
nothing but net. All right?
masuk mulus. Oke?
If I hit this one,
Jika ini masuk,
you have to give me playing time. Huh?
kau harus memberiku waktu main. Ya?
Okay, yeah. We'll see.
Oke, ya. Kita lihat saja.
Pack it up.
Kemas barangmu.
Ah. You missed.
Ah. Kau meleset.
Come on, we gotta fly. Plane leaves in 30.
Ayo, kita harus terbang. Pesawat berangkat 30 menit lagi.
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Gila ♪
♪ Wait till the world's all mine ♪
♪ Tunggu saat dunia jadi milikku ♪
♪ It's gonna be crazy ♪
♪ Pasti akan gila ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Gila ♪
♪ Everything I survived I must be crazy ♪
♪ Apapun yang kutahan Aku pasti gila ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Gila ♪
I really had to hustle back there, but...
Aku harus berlari kembali ke sana, tapi...
Yo! What?
Yo! Apa?
We're on a PJ?
Kita naik jet pribadi?
What? Oh, sick.
Apa? Oh, mantap.
- Are you seeing this? Oh, no. - You got dunked on!
- Kalian lihat ini? Oh, jangan. - Kau kena dunk!
Are y'all playing Roar 2K?
Kalian main Roar 2K?
It's so disrespectful!
Benar-benar tak sopan!
- Not just to me... - ...but to all birds.
- Tak cuma padaku... - ...tapi ke semua burung.
Auntie Olivia is not giving bird. Birds fly.
Bibi Olivia tidak menyerah. Burung terbang.
Are you broken?
Kau rusak?
Hey, hey, uh,
Hei, hei, uh,
Auntie Olivia has a condition
Bibi Olivia punya penyakit
called flightless bird syndrome.
sindrom burung tak bisa terbang.
Aw. Auntie Olivia can't fly.
Aw. Bibi Olivia tak bisa terbang.
But we can! Oh, no! Not the cockpit!
Tapi kami bisa! Oh, jangan! Jangan ke kokpit!
Girls!
Anak-anak!
We're taking over this plane!
Kami ambil alih pesawat ini!
- Reporting for duty! - No, don't touch that!
- Melapor untuk bertugas! - Jangan sentuh itu!
At least the bags are comfy.
Setidaknya tas ini nyaman.
Hey, Lenny. Is this seat taken? Yep.
Hei, Lenny. Kursi ini ada yang tempati? Ya.
- By who? - By me.
- Siapa? - Aku.
Ooh, that's good.
Ooh, baguslah.
Are you really trying to body-shame me
Apa kau mencoba mengejek tubuhku
for needing two seats?
karena butuh dua kursi?
Sorry. My bad.
Maaf. Salahku.
Hey, Modo. Is this seat taken?
Hei, Modo. Kursi ini kosong?
Eh. Technically speaking, nah.
Eh. Secara teknis, tidak.
What the... Ew.
Apa yang... Ew.
Oh. That's just my skin.
Oh. Itu cuma kulitku.
Ugh. Okay. There you go.
Ugh. Oke. Silakan.
Jett!
Jett!
Hey.
Hei.
So, you were shooting arou with the kid.
Kau tanding menembak dengan bocah itu.
Jett! He's good, huh?
Jett! Dia hebat, ya?
My mama could make those shots, okay?
Ibuku bisa masukkan tembakan itu, oke?
Doesn't mean he can play.
Bukan berarti dia bisa main.
Hey, Jett!
Hei, Jett!
I made it. Huh?
Aku berhasil. Ya?
Hey, everyone, a round of applause.
Semuanya, beri tepuk tangan.
Will made it.
Will berhasil.
Oh. Spicy.
Oh. Pedasnya.
Is following me around being annoying
Apakah terus mengikutiku dan menyebalkan
your full-time job, or...
pekerjaan penuh waktumu, atau...
You-You-You have to open it.
K-K-Kau harus membukanya.
The nuts, they're inside the can.
Kacangnya ada di dalam kaleng.
Wait. So the can isn't the food?
Tunggu. Jadi kalengnya bukan makanan?
Mane dropped a...
Mane rilis...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, jangan, tidak, tidak!
Mane just dropped a diss track about goat bo
Mane baru saja merilis lagu hinaan untuk bocah kambing itu.
Oh, Olivia, put it on the big screen.
Oh, Olivia, tampilkan di layar besar.
-Wait! No, wait. -You got it, Miss Lady Girl.
-Tunggu! Tidak, tunggu. -Tentu saja, Nona Manis.
-Modo's still sleeping. -Actually, I'm wide awake.
-Modo masih tidur. -Sebenarnya, aku sudah bangun.
I am here for this. Let's go!
Aku siap untuk ini. Ayo!
-Oh, yeah! Let's hear that one. -Oh, no.
-Oh, ya! Mari kita dengar. -Oh, jangan.
Oh, yes.
Oh, ya.
No, please! No, no, no.
Tidak, kumohon! Tidak, tidak, tidak.
You're not ready.
Kalian belum siap.
It's Mane season!
Ini musimnya Mane!
You know what's in my cup!
Kau tahu isi gelasku!
♪ I know you think You're all "ba-a-ad" ♪
♪ Kutahu kau pikir Kau sudah "mengembik" ♪
♪ But I'ma have you crying Like "ba-a-a" ♪
♪ Tapi kubuat kau menangis Sampai "mengembik" ♪
♪ You just goat here, I'm The Mane Attraction, though ♪
♪ Kau cuma kambing, tapi akulah Atraksi Utamanya ♪
♪ I'm the Godfather Call me Pony Soprano ♪
♪ Aku Ayah Baptisnya Panggil aku Poni Soprano ♪
♪ I'ma keep it short Just like you ♪
♪ Akan kubuat singkat Persis sepertimu ♪
♪ Next time we on the court The smoke's on you ♪
♪ Lain kali di lapangan Akan kuhancurkan kau ♪
♪ Act tough, but you're scared I'm in your nightmares ♪
♪ Sok tangguh, tapi kau takut Aku ada di mimpi burukmu ♪
♪ Tonight, when you sleep You'll be crying ♪
♪ Malam ini, saat kau tidur Kau akan menangis ♪
♪ Goat tears, goat tears ♪
♪ Air mata kambing ♪
♪ You'll be crying Goat tears, goat tears ♪
♪ Kau akan menangis Air mata kambing ♪
Oh, that is a banger!
Oh, itu lagu yang keren!
Eh, the lyrics are kinda mid.
Eh, liriknya biasa saja.
♪ You'll be crying Goat tears, goat, goat ♪
♪ Kau akan menangis Air mata kambing, kambing ♪
Goat tears, goat ♪
Air mata kambing ♪
♪ Tasty Goat, you'll be crying
♪ Kambing Enak, kau 'kan nangis
Yo!
Yo!
It smells so good in here.
Wanginya enak sekali.
This... this is where I wanna be at.
Ini... di sinilah tempat yang kuinginkan.
What is that? I've never... This could be in a room?
Apa itu? Aku tak pernah... Ini bisa ada di kamar?
Yeah, baby! We chilling in a penthouse!
Ya, Sayang! Kita bersantai di griya tawang!
We chilling in a penthouse.
Kita bersantai di griya tawang.
We chilling in a pent...
Kita bersantai di...
Oh! This is crazy!
Oh! Ini gila!
Hey! Look who it is!
Hei! Lihat siapa ini!
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Tunggu, tunggu, tunggu.
You guys ain't gonna believe this place.
Kalian takkan percaya tempat ini.
You see that? Aight.
Lihat itu? Oke.
Unsanitary, but it's cool.
Kotor, tapi keren.
Stop, stop, stop. Bad toilet, bad toilet.
Hentikan, hentikan. Kloset nakal.
And last but not least, TV in the minibar.
Dan terakhir tapi tak kalah penting, TV di bar mini.
Ooh!
Ooh!
You said courtside?
Kau bilang sisi lapangan?
Well...
Yah...
...you know, with the way things have been going,
...kau tahu, dengan keadaan sekarang ini,
if I'm even still on the team in a week,
jika aku masih di tim dalam seminggu,
I mean, I'll try to find you some tickets.
Maksudku, akan kucoba carikan tiket.
Are you kidding me, bro?
Kau bercanda, Bung?
What do you mean,
Apa maksudmu,
if you're going to be on the team next week?
jika kau masih di tim minggu depan?
You're on the actual Thorns.
Kau pemain Thorns sungguhan.
Ain't nobody kicking our boy off the team.
Tak ada yang akan menendangmu dari tim.
Nope.
Tidak akan.
All right, that's it. I need to hear it.
Baiklah, cukup. Aku ingin mendengarnya.
- Hear what? - Oh, you know what.
- Dengar apa? - Oh, kau tahu apa.
What? Oh, come on.
Apa? Oh, ayolah.
Do it.
Lakukan.
With feeling.
Dengan perasaan.
What is that noise? Give me that!
Suara apa itu? Kembalikan!
Jett...
Jett...
-Fillmore.
-Fillmore.
Your head is so green--
Kepalamu hijau sekali--
Keep it down.
Diamlah.
Uh, Jett, Jett. What?
Uh, Jett, Jett. Apa?
Um, I was hoping, up to you,
Um, kuharap, terserahmu,
I could get a little playing time? Eh?
aku bisa dapat sedikit waktu main? Eh?
Oh, that's all? Mmm? Mmm?
Oh, itu saja? Mmm? Mmm?
Just a little time on the court?
Hanya sedikit waktu di lapangan?
Oh, kiddo. All you had to do was ask.
Oh, Nak. Kau hanya perlu minta.
Really?
Benarkah?
And we're back at the Sunken City Cave,
Dan kita kembali ke Gua Kota Tenggelam,
where stalactites are falling from the ceiling,
tempat stalaktit berjatuhan dari langit-langit,
and the Thorns are at risk of
dan Thorns berisiko
falling out of playoff contention.
tersingkir dari pertarungan playoff.
Marshy! Marshy! Marshy!
Marshy! Marshy! Marshy!
Whoa! Hey!
Whoa! Hei!
-Foul. Number three, Fillmore. -Are you serious right now?
-Pelanggaran. No. 3, Fillmore. -Kau serius?
Now you blow the whistle?
Baru sekarang meniup peluit?
One more word and it's a technical!
Satu kata lagi dan itu pelanggaran teknis!
Why don't you take that whistle...
Sebaiknya kau ambil peluit itu...
...and stick it right up your cloaca.
...dan masukkan saja ke kloakamu.
Well, it's as close as you can get to saying butth--
Yah, itu sedekat mungkin dengan mengumpat pant--
I could have won this one.
Aku bisa menangkan ini.
- Get up. - Oh, no.
- Bangun. - Oh, tidak.
-This feels bad. -What are you waiting for?
-Ini terasa buruk. -Tunggu apa lagi?
O-Oh, my gosh.
O-Oh, Tuhan.
You're putting me in?
Kau akan mainkanku?
You think I want to? I don't have a choice.
Kau pikir aku mau? Aku tak punya pilihan.
Otherwise we forfeit the game.
Kalau tidak, kita didiskualifikasi.
They're putting in Will!
Mereka mainkan Will!
What?
Apa?
Hey, it's bedtime. I thoug I told you kids to--
Hei, saatnya tidur. Kupikir aku menyuruh kalian--
Things are starting to get ugly for the Thorns.
Keadaan mulai memburuk bagi Thorns.
You are the authority on ugly, Chuck!
Kau ahlinya soal memburuk, Chuck!
Will, Will, Will, Will, Will.
Will, Will, Will, Will, Will.
Oh, scoot over. I gotta watch this.
Oh, geser. Aku harus lihat ini.
Just remember, an opportunity like this is fleeting.
Ingatlah, peluang seperti ini cuma sesaat.
But public humiliation, that lives forever.
Tapi rasa malu, itu bertahan selamanya.
Really? That's your pep talk?
Serius? Itu kata-kata semangatmu?
What? I... I haven't coached in a while.
Apa? Aku... Sudah lama tak melatih.
I'm sorry. I'm a little out of practice.
Maaf. Aku kurang latihan.
- Who says that? - The whole planet's watching.
- Siapa bilang begitu? - Seluruh dunia menonton.
Oh. That's worse. Don't listen to me.
Oh. Itu lebih buruk. Jangan dengarkan aku.
What a beautiful moment.
Momen yang indah.
The first small to play in Roar.
Si mungil pertama yang main di Roar.
Yo, are you guarding me or my shoelaces?
Yo, kau jaga aku atau tali sepatuku?
I knew jerseys shrunk in the wash,
Kutahu jersei bisa menyusut saat dicuci,
but I didn't know the players did too! Aw.
tapi tak tahu pemainnya juga! Aw.
You're gonna end up roadkill, kid.
Kau akan berakhir menjadi bangkai, Nak.
Yo, Archie! Pick left!
Yo, Archie! Pilih kiri!
-Switch it up! -Hey, goat, good looking out!
-Tukar! -Hei, kambing, awas!
Archie with a big block.
Archie dengan blokan keras.
- I got it. I got it. - And Lenny recovers.
- Aku dapat. Aku dapat. - Dan Lenny merebutnya.
Will Harris is heading down the court.
Will Harris menuju area lawan.
Lenny! Hey, hey! I'm over here. I'm open. I'm open.
Lenny! Hei, hei! Aku di sini. Aku bebas. Aku bebas.
Lenny looking for somebody,
Lenny mencari teman,
- anyone who's not a goat. - Lenny!
- siapa saja yang bukan kambing. - Lenny!
Nowhere to go but Harris.
Hanya bisa oper ke Harris.
Lenny really doesn't wanna throw that pass!
Lenny sungguh tak ingin melakukan operan itu!
Let's go!
Ayo!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Tidak, tidak, tidak.
Shoot it, kid!
Tembak, Nak!
Will just scored!
Will mencetak angka!
Will Harris becomes the first small
Will Harris menjadi si mungil pertama
ever to score a point in Roar!
yang mencetak angka di Roar!
Did he just...
Apa dia baru saja...
- Too easy! - Hey!
- Terlalu mudah! - Hei!
Did I upset the little goat?
Apa aku membuat kambing kesal?
Who wants goat tears?
Siapa mau air mata kambing?
♪ Goat tears You'll be crying goat tears ♪
♪ Air mata kambing Kau menangis air mata kambing ♪
What? Oh, come on.
Apa? Oh, ayolah.
Will! Hey, Will! Run Eagle 24.
Will! Hei, Will! Gunakan Rajawali 24.
Thorns! Let's huddle up.
Thorns! Ayo kumpul.
What do we do? W-What are we gonna do?
Apa yang harus kita lakukan? A-Apa yang akan kita lakukan?
Coach wants us to run Eagle 24.
Pelatih mau pakai Rajawali 24.
We all know the play? Uh, no.
Semua tahu taktiknya? Uh, tidak.
-I do. -I've eaten 24 eagles.
-Tahu. -Pernah kumakan 24 rajawali.
Excuse me, what? What?
Permisi, apa? Apa?
Okay, Lenny. It's just you and me.
Oke, Lenny. Hanya kau dan aku.
I'm feeling something.
Aku merasakan sesuatu.
I can't even describe it. It's like I'm jittery.
Sulit dijelaskan. Seperti gelisah.
-Yeah. That's adrenaline. -I kind of like it.
-Ya. Itu adrenalin. -Aku menyukainya.
Put the ball in play, or I'm calling a delay of game.
Mulai permainannya, atau kuberi penalti.
Okay. Let's do this.
Oke. Mari lakukan.
Run whatever play you want, goat.
Gunakan taktik apa pun, kambing.
I'm locking you down.
Aku akan menguncimu.
Come on, kid.
Ayo, Nak.
Will!
Will!
Thorns win!
Thorns menang!
Yeah! We just did that!
Ya! Kita berhasil!
-Lenny, yeah! -All right! Yeah!
-Lenny, ya! -Bagus! Ya!
Smalls in the building!
Si mungil beraksi!
Harris might be a small, but he came up big!
Harris memang kecil, tapi dia bisa tampil besar!
- Yeah!
- Ya!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo!
I'm so happy, I could cry.
Aku sangat bahagia sampai mau menangis.
Come on, Gerald. Let me see it.
Ayo, Gerald. Biar kulihat.
Yeah, okay.
Ya, oke.
Yeah! Let's go!
Ya! Ayo!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, ya!
-Night, night, baby! -No!
-Malam, Sayang! -Tidak!
-Anxious happy energy! -Yeah!
-Energi bahagia yang gelisah! -Ya!
Anxious happy energy!
Energi bahagia yang gelisah!
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam! Akar menghujam!
Come on, Jett. We won.
Ayo, Jett. Kita menang.
Who wants to throw Dennis?
Siapa mau lempar Dennis?
It's like they say, Chuck.
Seperti kata orang, Chuck.
You mess with the goat,
Berurusan dengan kambing,
you get a stalactite to the face.
wajahmu kena stalaktit.
That's not a catchphrase.
Itu bukan ungkapan.
Get off my cloaca, Chuck!
Singkirkan dari kloakaku, Chuck!
Whatever. Whatever.
Terserahlah.
I mean, I scored 33, but who's keeping track?
Aku mencetak 33 angka, tapi siapa yang peduli?
What... Is it lame to search yourself?
Apa... Anehkah mencari nama sendiri?
It is. I know. I can't help myself.
Ya. Aku tahu. Tak bisa kutahan.
Yo, goat. Nice work tonight.
Yo, kambing. Kerja bagus malam ini.
You wanna join?
Mau gabung?
-Who, me? -Come on.
-Siapa, aku? -Ayolah.
Get to know your teammates a little.
Kenali rekan setimmu sedikit.
We don't bite.
Kami tak menggigit.
Well, Modo does sometimes.
Yah, Modo kadang begitu.
Just get in here.
Masuklah.
We're extending an olive branch here.
Kami tawarkan perdamaian di sini.
Well, I am grabbing that olive branch.
Tentu, kuterima perdamaian itu.
Shy? This kid's got ice in his veins, raining treys.
Malu? Anak ini punya mental baja, mencetak tiga angka.
Honestly, when Jett crashed out of the game,
Sejujurnya, saat Jett dikeluarkan dari laga,
I thought it was over.
kukira semua sudah tamat.
Oh, for sure. But the goat came through.
Oh, tentu saja. Tapi kambing unjuk gigi.
My guy!
Jagoanku!
I didn't even need my bucket tonight.
Aku tak perlu menampung muntahan malam ini.
This is so cool!
Ini sangat keren!
All right. All right. Uh...
Baiklah. Baiklah. Uh...
Uh, should we ask Jett to play?
Uh, haruskah kita minta Jett main?
Hey! You trying to ruin the one piece of fun we got?
Hei! Kau mencoba merusak satu-satunya hal menyenangkan?
We won without Jett.
Kita menang tanpa Jett.
I can't believe we're actually talking like this.
Tak percaya kita benar-benar bicara seperti ini.
She could be listening.
Dia bisa saja dengar.
What? Why?
Apa? Kenapa?
When we win, she likes to be the one that won the win.
Saat kita menang, dia suka menjadi pahlawannya.
She's a winner, and she's going to get us to the playoffs.
Dia juara, dan dia akan membawa kita ke *playoff*.
We got lucky for one game.
Kita beruntung satu laga.
Let's not go mad.
Jangan senang dulu.
I appreciate the optimism, but look at this team.
Aku hargai optimismemu, tapi lihat tim ini.
We got Coach Dennis at the helm.
Kita punya Pelatih Dennis sebagai nakhoda.
I think he dies when he sleeps.
Menurutku dia mati saat tertidur.
Me? I'm just trying to focus on my sweet baby angels.
Aku? Aku cuma mencoba fokus pada malaikat kecilku.
Incoming!
Awas!
-Oh, my gosh. -Everybody just sees me
-Oh, astaga. -Semua orang cuma menganggapku
as a tall rebound robot.
sebagai robot *rebound*.
At a certain point, I just checked out.
Pada titik tertentu, aku sudah menyerah.
I started finding other ways to be creative.
Aku mulai mencari cara lain untuk kreatif.
Lenny is a rapper.
Lenny seorang *rapper*.
Ah, Olivia, stop trying to put me on front stree
Ah, Olivia, berhenti mencoba mempermalukanku.
You know it's nothing I take too seriously.
Kau tahu aku tak anggap seserius itu.
Okay, maybe I take it a little seriously.
Oke, mungkin agak serius sedikit.
And I'm a bust. Maybe the biggest in Roar history.
Dan aku pecundang. Mungkin terbesar di sejarah Roar.
Come on now, Liv. That ain't true.
Ayolah, Liv. Itu tidak benar.
It is. You can say it.
Benar. Kau bisa katakan.
What else do you call a number-one pick
Mau sebut apa lagi pilihan pertama
whose biggest claim to fame
yang pencapaian terbesarnya
is being on someone else's poster?
adalah dipermalukan menjadi pajangan lawan?
Olivia?
Olivia?
Listen. Point is, this squad is a bunch of head cases,
Dengar. Intinya, tim ini berisi orang gila,
has-beens, and whatever the heck Modo is.
kedaluwarsa, dan apa pun wujud Modo ini.
Modo is icon.
Modo itu ikonik.
All right, Care Bear. Bets are in.
Baiklah, Care Bear. Taruhan dimulai.
What you got?
Apa punyamu?
I fold.
Aku menyerah. Aku mundur.
Ah! Uno reverse.
Ah! *Uno reverse*.
Yeah, they're the absolute worst.
Ya, mereka benar-benar yang terburuk.
-Oh. Oh, hi! -Oh, hi, Flo.
-Oh. Oh, hai! -Oh, hai, Flo.
-Hey, Flo! -Hi, Flo.
-Hei, Flo! -Hai, Flo.
- Hey, boss. - Hi, piglet.
- Hei, Bos. - Hai, anak babi.
Ugh. Hi, Modo.
Ugh. Hai, Modo.
Anyways...
Ngomong-ngomong...
Great team win last night.
Kemenangan tim yang hebat.
Socials are blowing up, and I've got some exciting news.
Medsos heboh, dan aku punya kabar gembira.
Hey, is Jett there?
Hei, Jett di sana?
-Jett? -What?
-Jett? -Apa?
-Jett!
-Jett!
Oh, hi. You know that Jett promo tomorrow?
Oh, hai. Kau tahu soal promosi Jett besok?
Well, now you're all gonna be in it.
Nah, sekarang kalian semua akan ikut serta.
Oh, yeah. Oh, this is dope.
Oh, ya. Oh, ini keren.
In Vineland, our roots run deep.
Di Vineland, akar kami menghujam dalam.
Vineland didn't just invent the game of roarball.
Vineland bukan cuma menemukan olahraga bola raung.
We define it.
Kami yang menentukan arahnya.
No one gets by me in the lane.
Tak ada yang bisa melewatiku.
I don't play the long game.
Aku tak main jangka panjang.
I play the tall game.
Aku main tinggi.
and you're not sure why.
dan kau tak tahu sebabnya.
And I'm the best in the game.
Dan akulah yang terbaik.
It's the end of one era
Ini akhir sebuah era
and the beginning of another.
dan awal era lainnya.
It's my time now.
Ini waktuku sekarang.
And now, it's time to pass the torch to the new GO--
Dan sekarang, saatnya untuk oper obor ke legenda ba--
GOAT!
Kambing!
I'm sorry. I can't. I can't. I... This...
Maaf. Tak bisa. Tak bisa. Aku... Ini...
- My body is rejecting the word. - Cut!
- Tubuhku menolak kata itu. - Potong!
You know what, let's just take five.
Kalian tahu, mari kita rehat 5 menit.
Cut! Jett, baby, what's the problem?
Potong! Jett, Sayang, apa masalahnya?
The problem is I'm the GOAT.
Masalahnya akulah legenda sejati.
I'm not passing the torch
Aku tak mengoper obor
'cause I'm still playing.
karena aku masih main.
It's just a promo. It's a play on words.
Itu cuma promosi. Cuma permainan kata.
He's a goat but also wants to be the GOAT.
Dia kambing tapi juga ingin jadi legenda.
Just say the lines.
Ucapkan saja dialognya.
Are we all okay with this?
Apa kita semua setuju dengan ini?
Now, I want to see a show of paws.
Sekarang, aku ingin lihat tunjukkan cakarmu.
Raise 'em up! Who is okay with this?
Angkat! Siapa setuju dengan ini?
Oh, everybody? Okay.
Oh, semuanya? Oke.
Hey, Maximus, let's pick it up from "they define it
Hei, Maximus, mari lanjut dari "mereka yang menentukan
You got it, boss.
Siap, Bos.
Vineland didn't just
Vineland tak cuma
invent the game of roarball.
menemukan bola raung.
We define it.
Kami yang menentukan.
I block every shot.
Kublok tiap tembakan.
I'm unstoppable. I think.
Aku tak terhentikan. Kukira begitu.
And I think there is a power struggle happening.
Dan kurasa ada perebutan kekuasaan yang terjadi.
-The end of one era... -I'm the GOAT.
-Akhir sebuah era... -Akulah legenda.
...and the beginning of another that's even better.
...dan awal era baru yang lebih baik.
It's my time--
Ini waktuku--
-No, it's not. -Cut!
-Tidak, bukan. -Potong!
Just say the line, Jett.
Katakan saja, Jett.
the difference between figurative and literal.
bedanya kiasan dan harfiah.
It's a double goat meaning.
Kambing di situ makna ganda.
I don't care. I'm not saying it!
Aku tak peduli. Aku takkan mengatakannya!
And he's not saying it either!
Dan dia juga tidak mengatakannya!
And y'all don't even think about saying it. Capisce?
Dan kalian jangan coba-coba mengatakannya. Mengerti?
Vineland didn't just invent the game of roarball.
Vineland bukan cuma menemukan bola raung.
We define it.
Kami yang menentukan.
I just wanna be a good dad.
Aku cuma ingin jadi ayah yang baik.
I just wanna blow minds with sick rhymes.
Aku cuma ingin memukau orang dengan rima yang keren.
Whoever memes my beak,
Siapa pun yang menjadikan paruhku meme,
you will be hearing from my lawyer.
kalian akan berurusan dengan pengacaraku.
I don't even know the rules of roarball.
Aku bahkan tak tahu aturan bola raung.
I'm the GOAT.
Akulah legenda.
Not some little goat guy.
Bukan kambing kecil itu.
- It's a single goat meaning. - Cut!
- Itu makna kambing tunggal. - Potong!
Cut, cut!
Potong, potong!
Look, since you're not gonna say the line,
Dengar, karena kau takkan katakan kalimatnya,
why don't you just give us a little "Baa."
bagaimana kalau kau mengembik saja sedikit.
Oh, I am not saying that.
Oh, aku takkan mengatakannya.
Why do I bother you so much?
Kenapa aku sangat mengganggumu?
I'm the one who stepped up when you fouled out.
Akulah yang maju saat kau membuat pelanggaran.
We finally won,
Kita akhirnya menang,
and you weren't even on the court.
dan kau bahkan tak ada di lapangan.
Now I feel weird.
Sekarang aku merasa tak enak.
Is this how I make everyone feel?
Apakah ini perasaanku untuk semua orang?
You know what, superstar?
Asal kau tahu, Megabintang?
This looks like it's your promo now.
Sepertinya ini menjadi promosimu sekarang.
'Cause I'm out of here. Yeah.
Karena aku akan pergi. Ya.
Good luck selling tickets.
Semoga sukses jualan tiketnya.
Jett! Wait. I'm sorry, I didn't mean to--
Jett! Tunggu. Maaf, aku tak bermaksud--
I didn't sign up for that, all right?
Aku tak setuju dengan itu, oke?
Come on, Jett, it's just a promo.
Ayolah, Jett, itu cuma promosi.
It gets fans hyped for our game!
Itu membuat penggemar antusias untuk pertandingan kita!
But it's not.
Bukan itu.
It's how everyone treats me.
Itulah cara mereka memperlakukanku.
They all want me to pass the torch,
Mereka semua mau aku mengoper obor,
but I'm not done!
tapi aku belum tamat!
I'm still here! I'm still playing!
Aku masih di sini! Aku masih main!
We're still waiting on that Claw, Fillmore.
Kami masih menunggu Piala Claw itu, Fillmore.
You're better off on the bench.
Lebih baik kau duduk di bangku cadangan.
- What? - I love you, Jett!
- Apa? - Aku menyayangimu, Jett!
I just want my car. Where is my driver?
Aku cuma mau mobilku. Di mana sopirku?
Jett! Over here!
Jett! Sebelah sini!
- Follow me. - Jett Fillmore!
- Ikuti aku. - Jett Fillmore!
Hey, Jett. Why do you not win anymore?
Hei, Jett. Kenapa kau tak pernah menang lagi?
Hey, watch it!
Hei, awas!
Excuse me.
Permisi.
This way.
Ke sini.
Whoa. This kid can move.
Whoa. Anak ini gesit juga.
I've never broken the law before.
Aku tak pernah melanggar hukum sebelumnya.
I actually paid for both of our rides.
Sebenarnya sudah kubayar untuk kita berdua.
I just wanted to see you sweat.
Aku cuma ingin melihatmu keringatan.
It was so messed up back there.
Tadi itu sangat kacau.
I mean, they act like you've been losing forever!
Maksudku, mereka bertingkah seperti kau selalu kalah selamanya!
I don't know what's wrong with them,
Aku tak tahu ada apa dengan mereka,
b-but I remember the Furball game.
t-tapi aku ingat laga Furball.
That was amazing! You scored 70 points!
Itu luar biasa! Kau mencetak 70 angka!
Well, you know why they call it the Furball game, right?
Yah, kau tahu kenapa disebut laga Furball, 'kan?
Because I choked. I missed the last shot.
Karena aku gagal. Tembakan terakhirku meleset.
We didn't make the Claw.
Kita tak mendapat trofi Claw.
Ever since then, Vineland's got no love for Jett Fillmore.
Sejak saat itu, Vineland hilang rasa pada Jett Fillmore.
No love for Jett Fillmore?
Hilang rasa pada Jett Fillmore?
You're seriously gonna listen to a couple of haters?
Kau serius mau mendengar celotehan beberapa pembenci?
Where's the lie? Even I get it.
Di mana bohongnya? Aku pun tahu.
Next stop, Vineland City Center.
Pemberhentian selanjutnya, Pusat Kota Vineland.
Okay. Get up.
Oke. Bangun.
We're getting off right here.
Kita turun di sini.
Hey, there he is!
Hei, itu dia!
Oh.
Oh.
You come to pick up some extra shifts?
Kau datang untuk mengambil giliran tambahan?
Ah. I see you got jokes.
Ah. Kulihat kau suka melawak.
Come back empty-handed?
Kembali dengan tangan kosong?
You said you'd get me Jett Fillmore's autograph.
Katamu kau akan memberiku tanda tangan Jett Fillmore.
Oh, my gosh. It's Jett Fillmore.
Oh, Tuhan. Ini Jett Fillmore.
What's up, y'all?
Ada apa, kalian?
Jett said she'd never tried the pie,
Jett bilang belum pernah mencoba pai ini,
so I figured we'd pull up.
jadi kami putuskan mampir.
This is...
Ini...
Whoa.
Whoa.
Not bad, huh?
Tak buruk, ya?
Wait, is that my high school jersey?
Tunggu, itu jersei SMA-ku?
Dang, y'all are some crazy stalkers.
Sial, kalian penguntit yang gila.
What do we have here? No way.
Apa ini? Gila.
Is that you?
Itu kau?
My grandpappy came here from afar
Kakekku datang dari jauh
to help build the Greenhouse. Yes.
untuk membantu membangun Greenhouse. Ya.
That's little me right there in my diaper.
Itu aku saat kecil memakai popok.
W-Wow.
W-Wow.
We're gonna name our baby after you, Jett!
Akan kuberi nama bayiku sepertimu, Jett!
We're hoping she'll grow up to be just like you.
Semoga kelak dia tumbuh sepertimu.
Aw. Cute egg.
Aw. Telur yang manis.
Check this out!
Lihat ini!
Oh... Yeah.
Oh... Ya.
Um... It definitely looks like I am doing something.
Um... Aku memang terlihat sedang melakukan sesuatu.
I'm nauseous.
Aku mual.
It's like that every time I go to open my mouth,
Tiap kali aku membuka mulut,
it's like... ...here it comes.
seperti... ...akan keluar.
I can't even see straight. I knew it! I knew it!
Pandanganku kabur. Sudah kuduga! Sudah kuduga!
I could tell something was off.
Aku tahu ada yang aneh.
How did you get so sick?
Kenapa kau bisa sakit?
Look, I'm not gonna say it's true,
Dengar, aku tak bilang ini benar,
but I will say the delivery guy was wearing a Magma jersey.
tapi kurir makanannya memakai jersei Magma.
Coinkydink? You decide.
Kebetulan? Tentukan sendiri.
Drumroll, please.
Siapkan tabuhan drum.
Right? Right? I told you.
Benar 'kan? Sudah kubilang.
Oh, snap. The Fillmore 1's?
Gila. Sepatu Fillmore 1?
Where did you get these?
Di mana kau dapat ini?
A collector never reveals her secrets.
Kolektor takkan membuka rahasianya.
I got 'em from the store when they came out.
Kubeli di toko saat baru rilis.
I've been looking everywhe for these.
Kucari ke mana-mana sepatu ini.
O-Okay, how much do you want for 'em?
Oke, berapa harga yang kau mau?
Are you kidding me?
Kau bercanda?
Your money's no good here.
Uangmu tak laku di sini.
They're your shoe. Just take 'em.
Ini sepatumu. Ambil saja.
No. No.
Jangan.
Just bring back a Claw.
Bawa pulang saja piala Claw.
Bye, Jett!
Dah, Jett!
Later, y'all.
Sampai jumpa.
How did you know about that spot?
Bagaimana kau tahu tempat itu?
I, uh... I go there for the pie.
Aku... ke sana membeli pai.
It delivers every time.
Rasanya selalu mantap.
Oh.
Oh.
You were the delivery boy.
Kau dulu kurirnya.
Yeah, yeah. Was that a little too obvious?
Ya. Apa itu terlihat jelas?
Okay.
Oke.
The real reason I know the diner
Alasan sebenarnya aku tahu kedai itu
is because my mom used to work there.
karena Ibuku dulu bekerja di sana.
She was a huge Thorns fan.
Dia penggemar berat Thorns.
- Mom. - That's for every year.
- Bu. - Ini untuk tiap tahunmu.
Happy birthday, Will.
Selamat ulang tahun, Will.
Baby, you know you could wish for anything, so dream big.
Nak, kau boleh meminta apa pun, bermimpilah yang tinggi.
You're not just going to play roarball.
Kau takkan sekadar bermain bola raung.
You're gonna change the game.
Kau akan mengubah permainan ini.
Dream big.
Bermimpilah yang tinggi.
Then, she got sick.
Lalu, beliau sakit.
And Vineland stepped up for me.
Dan Vineland membantuku.
Roarball was where I went to get out of my head
Bola raung menjadi pelarianku untuk menenangkan pikiran
and just... play.
dan hanya... bermain.
Y-You know?
Kau mengerti?
And everyone thought I was tripping
Semua orang menganggapku gila
when I said I wanted to be a roarball player.
saat kubilang ingin menjadi pemain bola raung.
Everybody. Except for my mom.
Semuanya. Kecuali Ibuku.
And I want her to be right.
Dan aku ingin membuktikannya.
You got a lot of good folks behind you.
Banyak orang baik mendukungmu.
So do you.
Begitu juga kau.
See you at practice tomorrow.
Sampai jumpa di latihan besok.
Hey, yo. It's Mane season.
Hei, ini musimnya Mane.
Oh, no. Here we go.
Oh, tidak. Mulai lagi.
And you know, man, just at the barbershop
Kalian tahu, kawan, aku di pangkas rambut
with P-Dogg and Boogie.
bersama P-Dogg dan Boogie.
Let's get into it.
Mari kita bahas.
A lot of naysayers out there, folks,
Banyak pembenci di luar sana,
been talkin' about this big game the goat had.
membicarakan permainan hebat kambing.
Puttin' up a whole three points. He's trash.
Cuma mencetak 3 poin. Dia sampah.
Thorns are trash!
Thorns itu sampah!
And it ain't just the goat that's wack.
Dan bukan cuma kambing yang payah.
The whole team is cooked!
Seluruh tim ini sudah tamat!
-They trash. -Mm-mmm.
-Mereka sampah. -Mm-mmm.
Someone needs to shut this clown up
Seseorang harus membungkam badut ini
once and for all.
untuk selamanya.
It's the grandmama herself, Jett Fillmore.
Si nenek sendiri, Jett Fillmore.
Yo, yo, yo! Mane is on live with Jett!
Yo, yo, yo! Mane sedang siaran bersama Jett!
What? Let me see that.
Apa? Coba kulihat.
No way, bro-dents.
Mustahil, kawan.
Do you know what? I'm just surprised
Tahu tidak? Aku terkejut
you even know how to use your phone
kau tahu cara memakai ponselmu
for anything other than
selain untuk
reading a menu with the flashlight.
membaca menu memakai senter.
I'm surprised you can talk with teeth like that.
Aku terkejut kau bisa bicara dengan gigi seperti itu.
Your tongue over there lookin' like it's in jail.
Lidahmu di sana terlihat seperti dipenjara.
"Let me out. Let me out."
"Keluarkan aku. Keluarkan aku."
Oh!
Oh!
Jett's got bars.
Jett jago membalas.
I've been in the league five years,
Aku sudah di liga selama 5 tahun,
already got two Claws.
sudah meraih 2 piala Claw.
How many Claws you got?
Berapa piala Claw punyamu?
- Nada. - Ball don't lie. Ball don't lie.
- Kosong. - Bola tak pernah bohong.
Well, that's about to change.
Yah, itu akan segera berubah.
I don't know if you saw our last game,
Kalian lihat laga terakhir kami,
Archie is a beast,
Archie sangat tangguh,
Olivia got her confidence back,
Olivia sudah percaya diri lagi,
Lenny's a stopper
Lenny pandai mengadang
-and Modo is an icon. -Hey!
-dan Modo itu ikonik. -Hei!
The Thorns are about to win our next eight games
Thorns akan memenangkan 8 pertandingan berikutnya
and then, yeah, we're coming for the Claw.
dan ya, kami akan meraih Claw.
Only thing crazy is that Clydesdale hair
Satu-satunya yang gila adalah rambut kuda poni itu
that you got sewn into your head.
yang kau jahit di kepalamu.
The textures don't match.
Teksturnya tidak cocok.
Drag him, Jett.
Hancurkan dia, Jett.
Oh!
Oh!
You know I get sensitive.
Aku sensitif soal itu.
Oh! Jett!
Oh! Jett!
Wait till I get off this live. Hmm.
Tunggu aku usai siaran. Hmm.
You know what,
Asal kau tahu,
just like I wrecked that baby goat at the Cage.
seperti kuhancurkan kambing kecil itu di Cage.
Until then, keep Will and the Thorns out your mouth.
Sampai saat itu, jangan sebut nama Will dan Thorns.
These roots run deep!
Akar kami menghujam dalam!
Fillmore out.
Fillmore pamit.
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam dalam!
Yeah, mama!
Ya, Mama!
You said some pretty nice stuff about us.
Kau bicara hal yang cukup baik tentang kami.
I'm wondering why.
Aku bertanya-tanya kenapa.
Are you feeling okay?
Kau baik-baik saja?
It's the first time I've been tagged
Ini pertama kalinya namaku disebut
in something that didn't make me cry.
dalam hal yang tak membuatku menangis.
I don't trust it.
Aku tak percaya.
Did you mean it?
Kau serius?
Look, I meant every word that I said.
Dengar, aku serius dengan tiap ucapanku.
I really do need y'all.
Aku memang butuh kalian.
And it's time I finally acknowledged
Kini saatnya kuakui
that I've got some really good folks behind me.
bahwa aku punya orang-orang hebat yang mendukungku.
Yeah.
Ya.
Really?
Benarkah?
To show you how serious I am,
Buktinya,
I'm officially naming Dennis
Secara resmi kutunjuk Dennis
the new head coach of the Thorns.
jadi pelatih kepala baru Thorns.
But I'm already head coach.
Tapi aku memang pelatih kepala.
I know. But now, it's, lik for real this time.
Tahu. Tapi sekarang, ini untuk sungguhan.
You're gonna be head coach. Only coach.
Kau jadi pelatih kepala. Satu-satunya pelatih.
The team is yours, Dennis.
Tim ini milikmu, Dennis.
Let's go, baby. Give it up.
Ayo, kawan. Terimalah.
My therapist said this day would never come. Uh...
Psikologku bilang hari ini takkan pernah tiba. Uh...
Just give me a second.
Beri aku waktu sebentar.
Dennis, get it together. Get it together.
Dennis, kuasai dirimu. Kuasai dirimu.
Get. It. Together.
Kuasai. Dirimu.
I've been watching, learning, waiting for this day.
Aku sudah memantau, belajar, menunggu hari ini.
- I'm scared. - We like it.
- Aku takut. - Kami suka itu.
We are going to rip the heart out of this league
Kita akan cabut jantung liga ini
and make 'em look at it.
dan memaksa mereka menatapnya.
Nice.
Bagus.
Welcome to Dennis's world of pain.
Selamat datang di dunia penderitaan Dennis.
growing up with violent tendencies.
tumbuh dengan kecenderungan kasar.
Charge!
Serang!
They've gone full-tilt 365-days-a-year psychopath.
Mereka sudah jadi psikopat 365 hari setahun.
Actually, it's 364.
Sebenarnya, cuma 364.
We take Christmas off.
Kami libur saat Natal.
Stop thinking of yourself as an enforcer.
Berhenti anggap dirimu sebagai algojo.
You're a protector.
Kau adalah pelindung.
Your teammates are like your daughters too.
Rekan timmu juga seperti putrimu sendiri.
Protect them.
Lindungi mereka.
Hey, hands off my beautiful daughter.
Hei, jangan sentuh putri cantikku.
Good looking out, Archie.
Bagus sekali, Archie.
Wait, what did you just call me?
Tunggu, kau panggil aku apa?
Lenny, team after team used you for your height
Lenny, tim demi tim manfaatkan tinggimu
and threw you away.
lalu membuangmu.
So you lost your drive.
Kau pun hilang semangat.
Ten teams in ten years, Coach.
10 tim dalam 10 tahun, Pak.
Well, this team has your back.
Tim ini mendukungmu.
So stick your neck out for them.
Maka berkorbanlah demi mereka.
Now tear the roof off this mother!
Sekarang hancurkan lawan!
Bang!
Duar!
Nice one, Lenny. That's my squad.
Bagus, Lenny. Itu timku.
Ooh, I kind of like that.
Ooh, aku agak suka itu.
Olivia.
Olivia.
One second. I'm just...
Sebentar. Aku cuma...
Seriously, give me your phone.
Serius, berikan ponselmu.
-Oh, no. -You are never seeing it again.
- Oh, jangan. - Takkan kau lihat lagi.
Another phone?
Ponsel lagi?
Where are you getting all these phones?
Dari mana kau dapat semua ponsel ini?
Olivia, get your head out of the phone and into the game!
Olivia, lupakan ponselmu dan fokuslah bertanding!
Ugh.
Ugh.
You were drafted number one for a reason.
Kau terpilih nomor 1 karena suatu alasan.
The only thing holding you back is you.
Satu-satunya penghalang adalah dirimu sendiri.
You are still that bird.
Kau masih burung hebat itu.
I am that bird.
Aku burung hebat.
Will. Jett.
Will. Jett.
I'm gonna coach the scat out of you.
Aku akan melatih kalian habis-habisan.
- Dennis, there's kids here. - Scat! Scat! Scat!
- Pak Dennis, ada anak-anak. - Latihan! Latihan! Latihan!
Jett, remember these three words,
Jett, ingat 3 kata ini,
"Pass the ball."
"Oper bola itu."
-Like, let the ball go? -Jett.
- Maksudnya, lepaskan bola? - Jett.
You mean share? With the others?
Maksudmu berbagi? Dengan yang lain?
I don't think this lesson is for me.
Kurasa pelajaran ini bukan untukku.
- Trust your team. - Open!
- Percayalah pada timmu. - Kosong!
Jett, pass the ball.
Jett, oper bolanya.
I'm open.
Aku bebas.
- Pass it! - What?
- Oper! - Apa?
Jett. I got it. I got it.
Jett. Aku mengerti.
- Pass the ball, Jett. - No, no, no, no.
- Oper bolanya, Jett. - Tidak, tidak.
- Dennis. No, no, Dennis. - No, no, no. Dennis!
- Dennis. Tidak, Dennis. - Tidak, tidak. Dennis!
Yes! Yes!
Ya! Ya!
Now just do that 500,000 more times.
Lakukan itu 500.000 kali lagi.
You, big hairy guy.
Kau, pria besar berbulu.
Block everything that the kid throws your way.
Blokir tiap bola yang bocah itu lempar kepadamu.
And you, that's 12 feet of grizzly.
Dan kau, beruang setinggi 4 meter.
Figure it out.
Cari solusinya.
Blocked.
Terblokir.
-Blocked. -Dang.
-Terblokir. -Sial.
Hey. Blocked.
Hei. Terblokir.
Will, you gotta find a way to get your shot over him.
Will, kau harus cari cara melampaui tingginya.
And Modo--
Dan Modo--
Wait, wait. Say it with your mind.
Tunggu. Ucapkan dalam batinmu.
Message!
Pesan terkirim!
Yeah, yeah.
Ya, ya.
If you do all this, you'll be more than a team.
Jika kompak, kalian lebih dari sekadar tim.
You'll be a unit. Unstoppable.
Kalian adalah unit. Tak terhentikan.
Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam dalam!
"Goat Tears" is wack,
"Air Mata Kambing" itu payah,
and I can't let it stand.
aku tak bisa membiarkannya.
to say "thank you" for pushing us this far.
sebagai tanda terima kasih atas perjuanganmu.
Here you go, Ms. Fillmore. Can I get a picture?
Ini, Nona Fillmore. Boleh minta foto?
♪ I'm always at the top... ♪
♪ Aku selalu di puncak... ♪
No way.
Mustahil.
Nice to meet you, Theo.
Senang bertemu denganmu, Theo.
And this is for your dad.
Dan ini untuk Ayahmu.
♪ We not horsin' round With you, okay ♪
♪ Kami tak main-main Denganmu, oke ♪
Uno reverse. You like that, Modo?
Pembalasan telak. Kau suka itu, Modo?
- Give me some. - Uno.
- Mari bersulang. - Uno.
♪ Sorry, horsey Gotta roast ya ♪
♪ Maaf, Kuda Poni Harus mempermalukanmu ♪
♪ Looks like Mr. Pony Turnin' into Mr. Phony ♪
♪ Tampaknya Si Poni Menjadi Si Palsu ♪
Will.
Will.
Slamalamadingdong!
Nombok habis-habisan!
♪ That's my squad, hey That's my squad, hey ♪
♪ Itulah timku, hei Itulah timku, hei ♪
Olivia.
Olivia.
♪ I love my squad, hey ♪
♪ Kusayangi timku, hei ♪
Yo, Lenny!
Yo, Lenny!
♪ Shout out to my squad Throw me the alley-oop ♪
♪ Salam untuk timku Beri aku umpan lambung ♪
♪ I'm always at the top ♪
♪ Aku selalu di puncak ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm taller than The hoop ♪
♪ Karena tubuhku lebih tinggi Dari ring basket ♪
Horns on, everybody.
Semuanya, pasang tanduk.
Thorns have really found their groove.
Thorns benar-benar menemukan ritmenya.
And is it me, or is Modo looking different these days?
Apa cuma perasaanku, atau Modo terlihat beda sekarang?
Oh, yeah. He's a thirst trap, Chuck.
Ya, Chuck. Dia idola baru.
Go long for my skin.
Mendekatlah padaku.
Marry me, Modo.
Nikahi aku, Modo.
No, marry me!
Tidak, nikahi aku!
- Whoo! - Thorns! Thorns!
- Whoo! - Thorns! Thorns!
The Thorns punch their ticket to the Roar Four
Thorns mengamankan tiket ke babak 4 Besar
and are heading to the playoffs.
dan menuju ke playoff.
What a turnaround, Chuck!
Kebangkitan yang hebat, Chuck!
If I were Mane, I'd be shaking in my horseshoes
Kalau aku Mane, aku 'kan gemetar di sepatu kudaku
'cause the Thorns are coming for him.
karena Thorns sedang mengincarnya.
♪ Looks like Mr. Pony Turnin' into Mr. Phony... ♪
♪ Tampaknya Si Poni Menjadi Si Palsu... ♪
Do we have a deal?
Apa kita sepakat?
Good.
Bagus.
Coach Dennis, how about a comment
Pelatih Dennis, bagaimana komentar Anda
on this team's epic turnaround?
soal kebangkitan tim yang luar biasa ini?
How's it feel, Dennis?
Bagaimana rasanya, Dennis?
It feels like victory!
Rasanya seperti kemenangan!
♪ It's more than Meets the eye ♪
♪ Ini lebih dari sekadar apa yang terlihat ♪
Yay!
Hore!
Okay, didn't know an ostri could get that fly.
Tak tahu burung unta bisa sekeren itu.
I see you, Olivia.
Kulihat kau, Olivia.
You know what they say,
Kau tahu kata orang,
birds of a feather look fly together.
burung dengan bulu sejenis terlihat keren bersama.
If Modo were any more of a snack, he'd eat himself.
Jika Modo lebih memikat lagi, dia 'kan memakan dirinya sendiri.
Love it. Love it.
Luar biasa. Suka sekali.
Uh...
Uh...
I'll be right back.
Aku segera kembali.
Uh, anyone know where Jett is?
Ada yang tahu Jett di mana?
I'll go get her.
Aku 'kan menjemputnya.
From the Vineland Thorns,
Dari Vineland Thorns,
at guard, Jett Fillmore!
pemain bertahan, Jett Fillmore!
I sold this team.
Kujual tim ini.
The new Thorns are relocating to Sunken City.
Thorns yang baru pindah ke Sunken City.
I'm sorry, what?
Maaf, apa?
You're joking.
Kau bercanda.
Oh, I never joke about money, honey.
Aku tak pernah bercanda soal uang, Sayang.
I brought Will onto this team to put butts in seats,
Kubawa Will ke tim ini untuk menarik penonton,
but I didn't expect for you to actually win.
tapi tak kusangka kalian benar-benar menang.
I'm selling while the getting's good.
Kujual selagi harganya sedang bagus.
What's gonna happen to the team?
Apa yang 'kan terjadi pada tim ini?
Oh, they're all gone, sweetie. Cleaning house.
Oh, mereka semua diberhentikan. Pembersihan total.
And as for you...
Dan soal kau...
I made sure the new owners knew all about your worn-out body.
Kupastikan pemilik baru tahu soal kondisi fisikmu yang ringkih.
And surprise, surprise,
Dan tak mengejutkan,
they weren't about to waste money
mereka tak mau membuang uang
on an old, broken-down player
untuk pemain tua yang payah
who's never gonna win a Claw!
yang takkan pernah meraih trofi!
And tell the team to clean out their lockers after y'all lose.
Beritahu timmu untuk kemasi loker usai kalian kalah.
Enjoy your early retirement, Jett.
Nikmati masa pensiun dinimu, Jett.
Hey, good luck out there tonight.
Hei, semoga beruntung malam ini.
Jett, Flo sold the Thorns?
Jett, Flo menjual Thorns?
You listening in on my conversations now?
Kau menguping pembicaraanku?
- We need to go tell the team. - No,
- Kita harus beritahu tim. - Tidak,
we'll tell them after the game.
setelah pertandingan saja.
If we tell them now, they'll fall apart.
Jika sekarang, mental mereka akan jatuh.
This affects all of us.
Ini berimbas pada kita semua.
Who's team captain here? You or me?
Siapa kapten tim di sini? Kau atau aku?
Jett. After the game.
Jett. Setelah pertandingan.
Welcome to the Cryosphere.
Selamat datang di Cryosphere.
Tonight, the Shivers face the Thorns
Malam ini, Shivers menghadapi Thorns
in the semi-final game.
di babak semifinal.
The winner marches triumphantly to the finals
Pemenang melaju bangga ke babak final
to battle for a championship and eternal glory.
tuk berebut takhta juara dan kejayaan abadi.
The loser? Banished to the cold void of history.
Pecundang? Terbuang ke tong sampah sejarah.
This is not just a game.
Ini bukan sekadar laga.
It is a reckoning.
Ini adalah penghakiman.
Lenny, are you trying to get traded?
Lenny, kau ingin dijual?
Hey, hey, Jett, you good?
Hei, hei, Jett, kau oke?
Focus on the game.
Fokuslah bertanding.
Don't worry about it. We'll get the next one.
Jangan cemas. Kita balas nanti.
Olivia.
Olivia.
Next time you think about shooting, don't.
Lain kali jika ingin menembak, jangan.
And that's the half.
Babak pertama berakhir.
Maybe we should tell them now.
Mungkin sebaiknya beritahu mereka sekarang.
After the game.
Setelah pertandingan.
Don't hurt yourself, grandma.
Jangan cederai dirimu, Nenek.
Catch! Yeah!
Tangkap! Ya!
Oh! The icebreaker!
Oh! Pukulan telak!
And Harris is slow to get up.
Harris lambat tuk bangkit.
So much for that Claw.
Gagal sudah trofi itu.
Thanks.
Terima kasih.
Thorns are down by 15
Thorns tertinggal 15 angka
late in the fourth quarter.
di akhir kuarter 4.
What is going on out there?
Apa yang terjadi di sana?
Jett, tell them. They need to know.
Jett, beritahu mereka. Mereka berhak tahu.
What did I say?
Apa kukatakan tadi?
Flo sold the team to Sunken City.
Flo menjual tim ke Sunken City.
None of us are going with it.
Tiada yang ikut pindah.
Can she even do that? Is that even allowed?
Apa dia boleh begitu? Apa itu legal?
We were playing well. We just started jelling.
Kita sedang hebat. Baru saja kompak.
- She sold our team? - There are rules.
- Dia menjual tim kita? - Ada aturannya.
I thought you had a championship.
Bisa jadi legenda, malah...
Could have been a legend, instead...
Pemain payah yang takkan pernah raih trofi!
Just get me the ball.
Operkan bola padaku.
I'm not going out like this.
Aku tak mau kalah begini.
Don't you mean "we"?
Maksudmu "kita"?
I know that look.
Aku tahu tatapan itu.
What do you think you're doing?
Apa yang kau lakukan?
That's two. Thorns down by ten.
Skor masuk. Thorns tertinggal 10.
Come on.
Ayolah.
We got to D up.
Kita harus bertahan.
Somebody get a body on her.
Seseorang kawal dia.
Come on.
Ayo.
Pass!
Oper!
It's the Jett Fillmore show now.
Kini waktunya aksi Jett Fillmore.
Jett with the pull-up. Thorns down eight.
Jett menembak sambil lompat. Thorns tertinggal 8.
Heads up!
Awas!
That deficit is cut to five.
Selisih menipis jadi 5.
It's a one-point game.
Beda 1 angka saja.
Ball! Now!
Bola! Sekarang!
It all comes down to this!
Inilah penentu segalanya!
-Archie! -Give me that, small.
- Archie! - Berikan bolanya, Bocil.
Boost me!
Angkat aku!
Will Harris for the win!
Will Harris tuk kemenangan!
Yeah!
Ya!
Thorns win! Thorns win!
Thorns menang! Menang!
They're headed to the Claw!
Mereka melaju ke final!
to the finals.
ke babak final.
Wow. I-I'm done. Team's sold anyway.
Wah. Aku selesai. Tim pun sudah dijual.
Come on, girls.
Ayo, anak-anak.
I'm not sticking around for this.
Aku tak mau lama-lama di sini.
Modo as well.
Modo juga.
You used to be my favorite player.
Kau dulu pemain favoritku.
Until today.
Sampai hari ini.
What a turn of events.
Kejutan yang luar biasa.
The Thorns have a shot at the Claw,
Thorns meraih peluang juara,
but Vineland has lost their team.
tapi Vineland kehilangan tim mereka.
I'll tell you, Rusty, I would hate to be a Thorns fan
Kuberitahu, Rusty, aku tak mau jadi fan Thorns saat ini.
right about now.
Pasti sangat berat.
♪ There is freedom without ♪
♪ Ada kebebasan di luar ♪
♪ Try to catch the deluge In a paper cup ♪
♪ Coba tampung luapan itu di cangkir kertas ♪
♪ There's a battle ahead ♪
♪ Pertempuran ada di depan ♪
♪ Many battles are lost ♪
♪ Banyak perang yang kalah ♪
♪ But you'll never see The end of the road ♪
♪ Tapi kau takkan lihat ujung jalan ini ♪
♪ While you're traveling With me ♪
♪ Selama kau berkelana bersamaku ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ Hei kini, hei kini ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ Jangan bermimpi ini usai ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ Saat dunia menghimpit ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ Mereka datang menghampiri ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ Tuk pisahkan kita ♪
♪ We know they won't win ♪
♪ Kita tahu mereka takkan menang ♪
♪ Now I'm towing my car ♪
♪ Kuderek mobilku sekarang ♪
♪ There's a hole in the roof ♪
♪ Atapnya berlubang ♪
♪ My possessions Are causing me suspicion ♪
♪ Hartaku membuatku curiga ♪
♪ But there's no proof ♪
♪ Tapi tiada bukti ♪
♪ In the paper today ♪
♪ Di koran hari ini ♪
♪ But you turn right over To the TV page ♪
♪ Tapi kau langsung membuka halaman TV ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ Hei kini, hei kini ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ Jangan bermimpi ini usai ♪
Come on. Let's go!
Ayo. cepat!
I got it!
Aku dapat!
Whew! Yeah!
Whew! Ya!
No way. Wait, is that...
Mustahil. Tunggu, apa itu...
Hey, Will.
Hei, Will.
Goat? Ball.
Kambing? Bola.
Yo, shouldn't you be getting ready to face the Magma?
Yo, bukankah kau harus bersiap menghadapi Magma?
Did you not watch the game?
Kau tak menonton laganya?
I don't think Jett wants to play with us anymore.
Kurasa Jett tak mau main lagi dengan kita.
I'm willing to bet she does.
Kuberani taruhan dia mau.
Hey. Can we talk?
Hei. Bisa kita bicara?
I'm busy.
Aku sibuk.
-No, he's not. -Come on, come on.
-Tidak, dia tidak sibuk. -Ayolah.
-Give... Give me the ball. -Not happening. My ball now.
-Beri... Berikan bolanya. -Tidak. Bolaku sekarang.
I came to say I'm-I'm sorry.
Aku datang tuk minta maaf.
Okay. Well, you did it. So...
Oke. Kau sudah melakukannya. Jadi...
Please, just hear me out?
Kumohon, dengarkan aku?
I want to win.
Aku ingin menang.
I want to hold up that Claw
Aku ingin meraih trofi itu
and feel what it's like to be one of the greats.
dan merasakan menjadi seorang pemain hebat.
When Flo said all that stu about me being washed up,
Saat Flo bilang aku sudah habis,
it just... it-it...
itu... itu...
it just got in my head.
itu merusak pikiranku.
And I couldn't let it go because deep down,
Aku terus memikirkannya karena jauh di lubuk hati,
deep, deep down,
jauh sekali,
I'm scared she's right.
aku takut dia benar.
And I just panicked.
Aku pun panik.
And I did you all so dirty.
Aku jahat pada kalian semua.
- And I'm so... - ...sorry.
- Dan aku... - ...minta maaf.
You know, I really thought that
Tahu tidak, dulu kupikir
if I was holding a Claw at the end of the day,
jika aku meraih trofi pada akhirnya,
it wouldn't matter how I got it.
cara mendapatkannya tak jadi soal.
But when you think about it,
Tapi jika kau renungkan,
that's kind of all that matters.
hanya itulah yang terpenting.
But you know, you still owe the diner a Claw.
Tapi kau masih berutang trofi pada kedai itu.
It's gonna be hard to win without a team.
Sulit tuk menang tanpa tim.
I might know a few folks.
Mungkin aku kenal mereka.
- Dad. - Daddy clown!
- Ayah. - Ayah badut!
Oh, thank God.
Oh, syukurlah.
These girls are crazy.
Anak-anak ini gila.
Get me out of here. Quick, start the car!
Bawa aku pergi. Cepat, nyalakan mobil!
Sup, Olivia?
Apa kabar, Olivia?
Come on. We've got a game to win.
Ayo. Kita punya laga tuk dimenangkan.
Yes!
Ya!
This is what dreams are made of, Rusty.
Inilah isi sebuah mimpi, Rusty.
Teams become champions.
Tim menjadi juara.
Players become legends.
Pemain menjadi legenda.
-♪ Let's go ♪ -♪ Yeah ♪
-♪ Ayo ♪ -♪ Ya ♪
♪ Gimme the ball Gimme the ball, yeah ♪
♪ Beri bolanya Beri bolanya, ya ♪
-♪ Let's go! ♪ -♪ Oh, I'm 'bout to... ♪
-♪ Ayo! ♪ -♪ Oh, aku akan... ♪
-Go, Thorns! -The best day of my life.
-Ayo, Thorns! -Hari terbaik dalam hidupku.
I can feel myself getting invested.
Aku mulai merasa bersemangat.
Who cares? I'm here for it. Break my heart, kiddo!
Tak peduli! Aku siap menonton. Membuatku haru, Nak!
Come on, Will. Let's go!
Ayo, Will. Maju!
Go, Thorns! Go, Thorns!
Ayo, Thorns! Ayo, Thorns!
Tonight, Jett and Mane
Malam ini, Jett dan Mane
will finally answer the question,
akhirnya menjawab pertanyaan,
-who is the GOAT? -On three.
siapa legenda sejati?
And here we go, Chuck.
Mari kita mulai, Chuck.
Unbelievable!
Luar biasa!
Mane Attraction gets the tip over Lenny.
Mane berebut bola melampaui Lenny.
Mane drills one home,
Mane mencetak poin pertama,
sending a strong message to the Thorns.
memberi peringatan keras pada Thorns.
You're too small.
Kau terlalu mungil.
Come on, Will. Show 'em who's too small.
Ayo, Will. Tunjukkan siapa yang mungil.
Eyes on me.
Tatap aku.
Jett with the sweet pass.
Jett memberi operan manis.
Thorns respond.
Thorns membalas.
Yeah!
Ya!
As the first quarter comes to a close,
Saat kuarter 1 segera usai,
it's still anyone's game.
permainan masih sengit.
We should be frying these fools.
Harusnya kita melumat bodoh ini.
Take 'em out if you have to, but hold on to that lead.
Habisi mereka jika perlu, tapi pertahankan keunggulan.
Harris on a break!
Harris menyerang balik!
-Will, watch out! -Huh?
-Will, awas! -Huh?
Ow! Hard hit on Jett.
Ow! Benturan keras pada Jett.
No foul call.
Tiada pelanggaran.
What?
Apa?
Oh, no.
Oh, Tidak.
This injury could take you out permanently
Cedera ini bisa menghentikanmu selamanya.
if you put any more weight on this leg.
Kaki ini 'kan lumpuh jika kau paksakan.
Hey, hey. It's not your fault.
Hei, hei. Ini bukan salahmu.
But I think I'm done.
Tapi sepertinya aku selesai.
What are we gonna do?
Apa yang harus kita lakukan?
We can't win without Jett.
Kita tak bisa menang tanpa Jett.
What? Aw, we're all thinking it.
Apa? Kita semua memikirkan hal yang sama.
Look, "roots run deep," that's more than just a cheer.
Dengar, "akar menghujam dalam" bukan sekadar sorakan.
My mom told me to dream big.
Ibu menyuruhku bermimpi tinggi.
And for Vineland,
Dan bagi Vineland,
there is no dream bigger than bringing home a Claw.
tak ada mimpi yang lebih besar dari membawa pulang trofi.
This might be the last time Vineland Thorns ever play.
Mungkin ini laga terakhir Vineland Thorns.
And we ain't gonna go out like this.
Dan kita takkan menyerah begitu saja.
Yeah, you heard the rook.
Ya, kalian dengar pemula.
Is that-- Is that Jett?
Apa itu Jett?
-Did she just-- -Yeah, Jett!
-Apa dia baru saja-- -Ya, Jett!
Jett, Jett, Jett!
Jett, Jett, Jett!
A well-deserved standing ovation
Tepuk tangan meriah yang layak
for the legendary Jett Fillmore.
bagi legenda Jett Fillmore.
Welcome back, GOAT.
Selamat kembali, legenda.
Jett! Jett! Jett!
Jett! Jett! Jett!
Archie.
Archie.
Harris is on a tear.
Harris bermain beringas.
-Olivia! -I got this.
-Olivia! -Aku yang tangani.
I am that bird.
Akulah burung itu.
She can fly!
Dia bisa terbang!
I can fly!
Aku bisa terbang!
She can fly?
Dia bisa terbang?
Olivia Burke just posterized Mane!
Olivia Burke baru saja permalukan Mane!
I am losing my mind here!
Aku tak percaya ini!
Olivia!
Olivia!
-That's right. -Go, Livvy!
-Benar sekali. -Ayo, Livvy!
Go, Thorns! We can do it!
Ayo, Thorns! Kita bisa!
Smalls ball! Ostriches fly!
Bola si mungil! Burung unta terbang!
These are the Thorns we came to see!
Inilah tim Thorns yang kita nantikan!
Look who's the poster child now.
Lihat siapa yang jadi pajangan sekarang.
Time out, Magma.
Waktu habis, Magma.
Oh, word of advice? Stay off social media.
Saran dariku? Jauhi media sosial.
We gotta turn this around now.
Kita harus membalikkan keadaan.
- Where my Maniacs at? - Mane!
- Di mana para penggila Mane? - Mane!
Uh-oh, I think we've got some seismic activity.
Sepertinya ada guncangan hebat.
Just listen to that crowd.
Dengar suara penonton itu.
-They're going crazy. -Oh, yeah!
-Mereka menggila. -Oh, yeah!
Let's go!
Ayo!
-Archie's trapped. No way out. -I know the feeling, Rusty.
-Archie terjebak. Tak ada jalan. -Aku tahu rasanya, Rusty.
Jett can't save you now.
Jett tak bisa menolongmu.
-What? -You gotta call that!
-Apa? -Harusnya itu pelanggaran!
The zebra and the horse are working together.
Wasit dan si kuda bekerja sama.
- Boo! - Come on! That's a foul.
- Huu! - Ayolah! Itu pelanggaran.
What you gonna do about it, small?
Apa maumu, bocah mungil?
Hey, Mane!
Hei, Mane!
He's not a small.
Dia tidak mungil.
He's a medium!
Dia ukuran sedang!
Hey, break it up!
Hei, bubar!
Let me at him! Let me at him!
Biar kuhajar dia!
Relax!
Tenang!
off my teammates.
rekan setimku.
Get him, Daddy!
Hajar dia, Ayah!
Make him bleed!
Buat dia berdarah!
That's not what you want to see.
Itu tontonan yang buruk.
Speak for yourself.
Bicara saja sendiri.
Flagrant two. Number 34, ejected.
Pelanggaran berat. Nomor 34, keluar.
Are you kidding me? Mane started it.
Kau bercanda? Mane yang memulai.
- Where's his foul? - Cry about it.
- Mana hukumannya? - Menangislah.
The rules state Thorns need five players
Aturan mewajibkan Thorns punya 5 pemain
-or they forfeit. -Hit me again.
-atau mereka didiskualifikasi. -Pukul aku lagi.
I haven't played since my rec-league days,
Aku tak pernah main lagi sejak dulu,
but I guess I could--
tapi kurasa aku bisa--
Put me in, Coach.
Mainkan aku, Pelatih.
I got a game to win.
Kita harus menang.
Jett, you can barely walk.
Jett, kau bahkan sulit jalan.
No. We can't let you do this. You'll just make it worse.
Kami tak bisa membiarkanmu. Ini 'kan memperburuk keadaan.
You think they bought it?
Kau pikir mereka percaya?
Um, I do.
Kira-kira begitu.
I think we have about three seconds before they catch on.
Hanya ada 3 detik sebelum mereka sadar.
But that's all we need. You all ready?
Tapi itu sudah cukup. Kalian siap?
I've been trying to run a play like this all season,
Aku sudah ingin memakai taktik ini,
but some hothead kept interrupting me.
tapi ada si keras kepala yang terus menggangguku.
That's a great play.
Taktik yang hebat.
Yeah. It was worth the wait.
Ya. Penantian ini sepadan.
Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam dalam!
Thorns are down by 2 with 20 seconds on the clock.
Thorns tertinggal 2 angka dengan waktu 20 detik.
Jett's gonna lay it all on the line. What a competitor!
Jett pertaruhkan segalanya. Sungguh pejuang sejati!
Listen up. Double-team her.
Dengar. Kawal dia berdua.
Triple-team her if you have to.
Bertiga jika perlu.
Do not let her out of your sight.
Jangan lepaskan dia dari pandangan.
Jett's fighting an injury. The court is unstable.
Jett sedang cedera. Lapangan tidak stabil.
Do you still want her taking the final shot?
Masihkah ia jadi pilihan tembakan terakhir?
With fire and brimstone bringing judgment and wrath
Meski kiamat menghampiri kita semua,
Ah!
Ah!
Will!
Will!
Come on. Get past me.
Ayo. Lewati aku.
I don't have to.
Aku tidak perlu melakukannya.
Our bestie just won the Claw.
Sahabat kita baru saja meraih Claw.
- That's my boy! - Hold me, Daryl.
- Itulah jagoanku! - Peluk aku, Daryl.
For the first time in 50 years,
Untuk pertama kalinya dalam 50 tahun,
the Vineland Thorns are champions!
Vineland Thorns menjadi juara!
Miracles can happen, folks.
Keajaiban bisa terjadi, Kawan.
I love this game. And I love you, Rusty.
Aku suka olahraga ini. Dan aku sayang kau, Rusty.
Attaboy, Will! Mwah!
Anak pintar, Will! Mwah!
Honey!
Sayang!
Let's have another dozen kids.
Mari kita membuat 12 anak lagi.
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha!
Ten years, ten teams, one Claw, baby!
10 tahun, 10 tim, 1 Claw, Sayang!
We are champions!
Kita adalah juara!
-Daddy!
-Ayah!
You were so cool.
Ayah sangat keren.
Daddy was pretty cool, right? I was like...
Ayah memang keren, 'kan? Ayah seperti...
We love you. Mwah.
Kami sayang Ayah. Mwah.
Hey, Mane. Good game.
Hei, Mane. Laga yang bagus.
Let me help you up.
Biar kubantu bangun.
Hey, uh, your hair is on fire.
Hei, uh, rambutmu terbakar.
What? Oh, no. No. No.
Apa? Oh, jangan. Tidak.
Not the hair!
Jangan rambutku!
- Will! - Jett.
- Will! - Jett.
We're champions, baby.
Kita juara, Sayang.
Oh, Jett! We did it! We actually did it!
Oh, Jett! Kita berhasil! Kita sungguh berhasil!
No, you did it.
Bukan, kau yang berhasil.
Looks like Moms was right.
Sepertinya Ibu benar.
-J-Jett, you okay? You good? -I'm fine.
-Jett, kau oke? Baik-baik saja? -Aku oke.
I'm fine. I just can't feel my legs...
Aku oke. Cuma tak bisa rasakan kakiku...
...but I'm a champion, baby.
...tapi aku juara, Sayang.
Jett Fillmore passed the ball.
saat Jett Fillmore oper bola.
Security!
Keamanan!
Hold up, sucka.
Tunggu dulu, Bodoh.
Playtime? Should we destroy?
Waktunya bermain? Haruskah kita hancurkan?
Destroy!
Hancurkan!
Do you know who I am?
Kau tahu siapa aku?
Hey, you were right about Will.
Hei, kau benar soal Will.
He's a great addition to the team.
Dia tambahan yang hebat bagi tim.
Bye, piglet.
Dah, Anak Babi.
Introducing your Roar champions,
Memperkenalkan juara Roar,
the Vineland Thorns!
Vineland Thorns!
Yeah! Let's go, Vineland! Let's go!
Ya! Ayo, Vineland! Maju terus!
Horns up, everybody.
Pasang tanduk, Semuanya.
Vineland!
Vineland!
I think it's time they hear from...
Kurasa saatnya mereka mendengar kabar dari...
the GOAT.
sang legenda.
Will! Will! Will!
Will! Will! Will!
Medium fries did it!
Si Kentang berhasil!
I... I...
Aku... Aku...
I don't even know what to say right now.
Tak tahu harus bicara apa saat ini.
- This is crazy. - We love you, Will!
- Ini gila. - Kami sayang kau, Will!
Oh, wow, um...
Oh, wah, um...
I mean...
Maksudku...
I saw Jett play when... when I was just a kid.
Aku menonton Jett main saat masih kecil.
And you know what's crazy?
Dan tahu apa yang gila?
My mom actually believed it.
Ibuku sungguh memercayainya.
She always seemed to know those kinds of things, you know?
Ibu selalu tahu hal-hal semacam itu, 'kan?
Like she always knew that even if she couldn't be here for me,
Seperti ia selalu tahu bahwa meski ia tak bisa di sini,
Vineland would be.
Vineland 'kan selalu ada.
You delivered for me...
Kalian mendukungku...
Will done changed the game.
Will sudah merubah permainan.
And you always had my back.
Dan kalian selalu menjagaku.
And you inspired me.
Kalian memberiku inspirasi.
We brought the Claw home!
Kita membawa pulang trofi Claw!
And even if the Thorns
Dan meski Thorns
don't have a home in Vineland anymore...
tak punya rumah lagi di Vineland...
...no one can take this Claw away from us!
...tak ada yang bisa merebut trofi ini dari kita!
Vineland will be champions forever!
Vineland 'kan jadi juara selamanya!
Modo has something to say!
Modo ingin bicara sesuatu!
Thorns staying in Vineland!
Thorns tetap di Vineland!
Modo is team owner.
Modo adalah pemilik tim.
Wait. How?
Tunggu. Bagaimana bisa?
All in.
Pasang semua.
A-ha! Uno reverse!
A-ha! Pembalasan telak!
What? Let me take a look at that.
Apa? Biar kulihat itu.
You're giving this freak lizard the team?
Kau berikan tim ini pada kadal aneh ini?
Wow! This is actually legit.
Wah! Ini benar-benar sah.
Modo's my boss.
Modo bosku sekarang.
That's not good.
Itu tidak bagus.
Yeah, mama!
Ya, Mama!
- Marry me, Modo! - No, marry me!
- Nikahi aku, Modo! - Jangan, nikahi aku!
You hear that, Vineland?
Dengar itu, Vineland?
Looks like the Thorns are staying!
Sepertinya Thorns tetap di sini!
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam! Akar menghujam!
Roots run deep!
Akar menghujam dalam!
Thanks, Mom.
Terima kasih, Bu.